That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 9: Attack of the Ogres
Rimuru and the Goblins' development of
their village continued to progress.
Kaijin and the three Dwarf brothers,
Garm, Dord, and Myrd,
made clothing and tools and built more homes,
while the Goblin Lords under Rigurd worked
out a system for ruling the village.
Everything's going great!
Even without my orders,
everyone's doing their job.
Makes it easier for me!
Besides, there's something
important I need to do.
Good. No one's around.
There, all fixed.
Shizu-san, I'll take good
care of this keepsake of you.
Now, then...
Transform!
Mimic => Human
This Mimic works really smoothly.
An actual human body...
Feels great to have this.
Vision...
Hearing...
Actually, I think I could see and
hear things better as a slime.
Because of Magic Sense?
So, next...
Hey, Great Sage, since I ate Ifrit,
can I use body doubles now, too?
Answer.
Analysis Complete
All of Ifrit's skills, including
Body Double, have been analyzed.
All of Ifrit's skills,
including
Body Double,
have been analyzed.
All right, great!
I'll try it out right now.
Body Double!
Body Double
I see... It does look like Shizu-san.
No trace at all of how I
looked when I was alive.
What a beautiful... boy? Girl?
Well, I need to know what sex my
body is when in human form, right?
Though I can kind of already tell...
But since I didn't actually
check to be sure...
My son didn't make it!
I seem rather androgynous...
In fact, I have no gender at all!
I'm sexless!
Well, I guess I had no
gender as a slime, anyway.
Wait... Now that I think about it,
when I took human form earlier,
I didn't see any black mist...
Answer.
Answer
When using Mimic to assume a
form larger than one's own,
black mist produced by magicule
consumption makes up the difference.
Black
Mist
Which means... I could
create an adult form, too!
All right!
Ooh! Can I make it look masculine?
Hey, he's pretty handsome!
Okay, now make it feminine!
Ooh!
Wait, stop! Stop! Go back!
I can't do that.
Giving myself an adult female form
makes me look like Shizu-san,
and that just feels immoral.
That concludes my report.
Okay, no problems. Good work.
Oh, also...
Are you sure you will
need no food again today?
Yeah, I can't taste anything
as a slime anywa—
Rigurd!
Yes?
I'm gonna eat with you guys starting today!
Truly?!
Then we must prepare a lavish feast tonight!
Yeah, do that!
Yes, sir!
That's right! Since I can
mimic a human form now,
I'm gonna eat all kinds of tasty food!
I wonder what's on the menu...
Meat, maybe? There'll probably be meat.
Which means I'll want rice, too...
Do they have rice plants in this world?
I'll have to look for some eventually.
If I find any, I'll make some rice fields...
Rimuru-sama!
Thanks for always getting our food for us.
Thank you, sir.
We're just on our way out to the forest.
We're having a feast tonight,
so bring back some tasty prey!
Are you going to eat with us today?
Sure am!
This body has a sense of taste, after all.
If you eat a lot, I wonder if
your boobs will get bigger...
I'm sorry! I'll make sure
Gobta is strictly disciplined!
Anyway, I will prepare some
grade-A bulldeer for the feast.
Bulldeer
Great! Thanks!
Just leave it to me.
Many magical beasts have been traveling
this way from deep in the forest, lately,
so prey is abundant.
Did something happen?
No, magical beasts move from place
to place as the environment changes.
I don't think it's anything serious.
You called, Master?
Ranga, go into the forest with Rigur's team.
I doubt anything will happen,
but just in case.
Understood. You can count on me.
No need for reservation, Rigur.
Take me along.
Wow, that was pretty cool, Ranga!
Even cooler if you weren't doing that...
I paid a visit to the cave
where Veldora had been sealed.
I wanted to test out Degenerate,
the unique skill I'd received from Shizu-san,
in a place where it wouldn't disturb anyone.
Regardless of the impression
given by the name "Degenerate,"
the skill was important to her,
and that makes it precious.
The skill...
Degenerate
uses unification and separation
to merge skills together,
evolving them into new skills.
In other words, she used it
to gain a bunch of new skills.
One of them was...
What is this? It's creepy...
This is the extra skill, Black Flame.
— Black Flame —
I'll have to be careful
how I use this one, too.
Still...
I should really be grateful to Shizu-san.
This mask has the power
to suppress magic, right?
Let's see.
How's this?
Answer.
Aura completely erased
The faint aura you were emitting
has been completely erased.
In this state, you would
be perceived as a human.
Magicule Level: 0
Perception: Human
Okay. I should wear this
when I go to new places.
Lookin' good!
Right.
You sound unimpressed.
Rimuru-sama!
Receiving Thought Communication from: Ranga.
Tempest Wolf
Thought Communication: Ranga
Vocal tone indicates that
it is a request for aid.
Tempest Wolf
Likely a request for aid
I'm gonna die! I'm dead!
What happened?!
I got cut! It hurts so bad!
Calm down. It's not deep.
Who are you guys?
Wait... Rimuru-sama, it's you!
You got worried and came to help?
Yeah, that's right.
You seem fine, so I guess
you don't need any potion.
W-Wait! I want some!
I'm sorry I joked around like that!
Th-That helped a lot!
Ranga!
Master, forgive me.
This happened while I was here...
Come back, Rigur!
G-Rimuru-sama... I am sorry.
Don't worry. Leave this
to me and get some rest.
Thank you...
Ranga, what happened to
the ones who've fallen?
They've been put to sleep with magic.
That pink-haired one did it.
Magic, huh?
Looks like these guys are gonna be trouble.
How humiliating. I never thought
we would run into Ogres.
Ogres?
The ones in games and
movies look like this...
But these don't look like that at all.
They even have armor on.
Also, those look like
Japanese swords to me...
Six Ogres...
Hey, you guys.
I don't know what happened,
but sorry about what my guys did.
Would you be willing to talk this out?
They're clearly much stronger,
but Gobta and Rigur weren't fatally wounded,
and most of our security force was
just put to sleep, not injured.
There must be something to it...
Well, I'll just have to be
the adult in the room and—
Show us who you really are, evil majin!
Huh?
Hey, hang on! What did you call me?
Enslaving monsters is not a feat
just any human can accomplish.
Huh?
You may hide your appearance and
suppress your aura, but it won't work!
Reveal your true identity.
For the mastermind to approach
us himself is most convenient.
Yikes!
But my true identity is
just a lovable slime...
Hey, listen, guys...
We have no intention of listening to you.
That mask tells us everything
we need to know!
My mask?
Wait a minute! Aren't you
making some kind of mistake?
This is just a keepsake of—
If it will serve to repay even
a billionth of what was done
to our brethren, we will have your head!
You friend of those evil pigs!
What shall we do?
Do? I mean...
You take care of the pink-haired one.
Yes, sir.
And don't kill her.
I think there's more to this.
Just get in their way a bit.
I'll take out the rest.
But that would mean you'd
be taking on five Ogres...
Not a problem.
I won't lose.
That's my master!
Understood!
You underestimate us.
Are you truly brave or just foolhardy?
Out of respect for your sheer nerve,
I'll go along with your provocation.
I hope you don't regret it later.
You can just take a nap.
— Paralysis Breath —
Sorry, but I saw you with Magic Sense.
Huge!
Wait, that's not what I meant by "I saw you!"
Don't get me wrong!
Looks like you're about to fall, miss.
Sticky Steel Thread
Joke!
— Body Armor —
Way to go!
He beat us that easily?
So, that just leaves...
What'll it be?
The Evil Centipede's Paralysis Breath...
The Black Spider's Sticky Steel Thread...
The Armorsaurus's Body Armor...
He may have learned the skills
of many other monsters, as well.
Do not lower your guard, young master.
He named all the skills I used,
and the monsters they came
from, from just one look...
I should try not to give too much away.
Can we stop this?
I'd like you to hear what I have to say now.
Quiet, evil majin!
Okay, um... So, listen...
I admit you are strong.
That makes me all the more certain.
Certain of what?
You are one of them!
Them? Who?
It is unthinkable for us Ogres
to be defeated by mere Orcs!
Orc?
H-Hang on, what makes you—
Quiet!
I know it was all the work of
you and your majin comrades!
Huh? Majin?
Don't deny it!
Wait! You've got the wrong—
I must be going senile.
I was certain I cut off your head.
Are they serious?
Rimuru-sama!
Y-Your arm!
Master!
I'm fine! Don't let your guard down!
Did he get under my Magic Sense
and easily break through my
Multilayer Barrier and Body Armor?
Next time, I won't miss.
Looks like you were just foolhardy after all.
I commend your courage to remain
calm after losing an arm.
The pride that compelled you to take
us all on alone will be your downfall!
Regret your folly in the next life!
— Ultraspeed Regeneration —
Did you think you'd beaten me just
by cutting off one of my arms?
F-Foul beast!
Ogre Flame!
Young master...
Did I... get him?
Too bad.
Fire has no effect on me.
You were right, though.
I did underestimate you.
I'll show you...
what I'm like when I'm serious.
What an aura...
Take a good look.
— Black Flame —
That's... That flame is...
It's not produced by using
the surrounding magicules!
The only thing forming that
flame is his pure strength!
And the size of the flame mirrors
the size of his power...
I'll show you something
even more interesting.
This is my true power!
Uh...
Maybe I should've kept this
one under wraps, after all...
What now? Still want to fight?
Good, he's scared.
Please just surrender now!
Young master, please take
the princess and flee.
I will end this.
Quiet, old man.
That is intense.
It saddens me to say it, but it
seems we are no match for you.
Still, I have my pride as the next
leader of the powerful Ogre clan!
And what leader would fail to
avenge his slain brethren?!
Even if I can't win, I will still fight back!
Young master, if you fight,
I will fight by your side!
That's their answer?
Well, damn. That backfired on me.
Wait, Brother!
This individual may not be our enemy!
Move!
No!
Why?
He's a masked majin, just like
the one who attacked our village!
You said so yourself...
Yes... but please, try to
think this through calmly.
Why would such a powerful majin
use such underhanded tactics
as forcing the pigs to attack our village?
It makes no sense.
He surely has the power to kill us
all on his own, if he so desired!
There is no doubt he is unlike us,
but I don't think he has any connection
to the ones that attacked our village.
Feeling a little more willing to listen now?
I don't need this anymore, right?
Who are you?
Me?
I'm just a slime.
A slime?
Yep. Rimuru the slime.
I-It's true...
And this mask is a keepsake
from someone I knew.
Feel free to see for yourself
whether it's the same one
that your attacker had.
All right...
It does seem similar, but...
This one contains anti-magic power.
But the majin from back then
wasn't concealing their aura...
Then...
Forgive us.
It seems our desperation caused
a grave misunderstanding.
Please accept my apology.
Sure, I accept.
Sheesh.
For a minute there, I wasn't
sure what was gonna happen.
Well, this is no place to talk.
Let's head back to the village.
Come with us.
Are you sure?
Yep.
I want to hear about what
you've been through.
But we wounded your companions.
And we did the same to yours.
But no one died, so we'll say it's all good.
Forgive us.
Besides, we're having a feast today.
The more, the merrier, right?
And so, the battle that began before
anyone even knew why had ended.
The Ogre princess reversed the sleep spell,
and the Goblins awoke.
Rimuru healed the Ogres'
wounds with his potion,
and the whole gang headed for
Rimuru and the Goblins' village.
By the way, what's your name.
Oh, we have no names.
Oh, yeah. I forgot, most of you don't.
That's right...
Next time, "The Orc Lord."
The Orc Lord