In hopes of saving the kids,
Rimuru took them in search
of the Dwelling of Spirits.
On the way, they met Ramiris,
the Queen of Spirits.
Then, after earning her agreement to help,
they set out to try to
summon superior spirits.
So this is...
The deepest part of the Labyrinth,
the Dwelling of Spirits.
Kenya, Ryota, Gale, Alice, Chloe...
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Shizu-san, wherever you
are, are you watching?
I'll make sure
your wish is realized.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 23: Saved Souls
Now, listen. You'll call to
the spirits from over there.
What do we say?
Anything. It can be, "Help me!"
Or even, "Let's play!"
If any spirits take interest and come
to you, the summon was a success.
Will they actually come?
Sure they will!
R-Right...
Sensei, they'll come, right?
They'll come?
It'll be fine. In the worst case...
I'll tame a demon if I have to.
Uh, your face looks really evil right now.
So, who's going first?
Sensei...
If anything happens to me, take care of them.
I can't wait to see what
kind of spirit shows up!
Okay, I'm going to pray now.
These aren't superior spirits...
They're inferior spirits.
If these tiny spirits
are fragments cut from a great
spirit by Gale's prayer,
then we just need to create a new spirit.
Great Sage.
Question.
Use Gluttony to consume
and unify the spirits?
Unify the spirits?
That's a yes, of course.
Gale, keep praying.
H-Hey!
You ate them?! How could you do that?!
Keep quiet and watch. I have an idea.
Go for it, Great Sage.
Notice.
Notice
Using the unique skill Degenerate,
Superior
Spirit
unification into a superior
spirit is complete.
Unification
Complete
All right!
Its attribute is earth.
Attribute: Earth
Creating auxiliary artificial personality.
Creating
Auxiliary
Artificial
Personality
Success.
Unify the completed artificial superior
spirit of earth with Gale Gibson?
Earth
Artificial
Superior Spirit
Gale Gibson
Unify?
Yes!
How's this? Appraisal.
His rampant energy is calming down.
He's got control.
Now, as his body matures,
he should gradually acquire abilities.
We did it, Great Sage!
Heh.
I feel like I just saw Great
Sage make a smug face...
You imagined it.
Okay, it's over. You did great.
Huh?
You're okay now. The destruction's stopped.
I guarantee it.
S-Sensei... Thank you so much!
Think nothing of it. It's only natural
that I'd protect my students.
Hooray!
Congratulations!
You did it!
That's great!
It's too soon to celebrate.
Save the parties for after
you're all successful.
Notice.
Notice
Using the unique skill Degenerate,
Superior
Spirit
unification into a superior
spirit is complete.
Unification
Complete
Its attribute is space.
Attribute: Space
Unify the completed artificial superior
spirit of space with Alice Rondo?
Yes.
Alice, you did great.
You'll be okay now.
Well, thanks!
All right! I'm next!
I haven't even started praying yet...
Is something coming?
Hey! How are ya?
I'm just great!
What the heck are you doing in my house?!
It was just a whim.
Who is that?
This is...
Hiya! I'm a light spirit! Nice to meet ya!
Unlike the evil spirit that
fell to become this monster
I'm a pure, innocent spirit of light!
Who are you calling evil?!
Kenya, it looks like you summoned
a superior spirit of light.
Wh-What?!
So your name's Kenya?
Okay, I'm gonna call you Ken!
I could just feel something shining in you, Ken!
I know, 'cause I'm light!
That wasn't funny.
So on that note, I'm gonna save you, Ken!
I'll look out for you
until you're all grown up!
You might even become a Hero, you know!
A Hero?!
Ken, a Hero?
Wow...
Well, that would be something...
It inhabited you...
Huh?
That easily?
Sensei...
Huh?
Oh, yeah! It's fine! All according to plan!
Good for you!
Er, uh...
Yeah!
Notice.
Notice
Its attributes are water and wind.
Attributes
Water
Wind
Creation of artificial superior
spirit of water and wind successful.
Artificial
Superior
Spirit
Success
Unify it with Ryota Sekiguchi?
Yes.
Just one left.
Sensei, um... Sensei...
Um, Sensei... um...
I love you!
Well, I like you, too.
I wish you'd waited another eight...
no, ten years to say that.
Hell, I wish I'd heard
that while I was alive!
Go on and pray.
Okay.
What's that?
That pressure...
It felt like the sky fell down.
That's... not a spirit?
Answer.
It is a spiritual body equivalent
to a superior spirit.
Abnormal level of energy detected.
Its threshold is immeasurable.
What the...
Hold it! No way, no how!
I'm not letting you have your way!
Hey, what the heck are you—
Quiet! That thing's dangerous!
Can't you see that?!
How the hell would I know?!
What's so dangerous?
We'll talk later!
It inhabited her!
Darn it! It's too late!
Well, I'm done!
Don't blame me for whatever happens!
Appraisal.
That immense energy has
completely disappeared.
She seems... stable.
Looks like there's no problem...
But what in the world...
So just what was that?
No idea! I don't know the details!
But I'm pretty sure that
one was born in the future.
Huh?
It's something resembling a spirit,
except it came from the future!
It's almost impossible to believe,
but by inhabiting her, it laid the
foundation for its own rebirth?
What are you talking about?
I seriously don't know!
But that thing had enormous power!
I'm pretty sure it'll be big trouble
if that thing is born in the future!
Maybe it had the divine protection
of the Great Spirit of Time...
I'm completely lost!
But it's all good. As long as Chloe's
okay, that's all that matters.
No one knows what'll happen in the
future, so it means nothing right now!
Good for you, Chloe.
It went just as I planned.
You're out of danger now, too.
Was that really just as you planned it?
Y-Yeah! Of course!
I mean, not that it matters.
Now that it's inhabited her,
it's out of my control.
What's the problem?
Everyone was successful.
Thanks! These kids are saved, thanks to you!
Thank you!
I'm grateful!
C-Cut that out already!
And this is a Demon Lord?
What has the world come to?
I did it, Shizu-san.
They'll be okay now.
It was a happy ending!
Or so I thought, but after that...
I had to give Ramiris a replacement
for the golem I destroyed...
Then I had to summon a demon and
make it possess that golem...
And there was one last struggle.
But hey, that's a different story.
I truly thank you.
Nah, no worries, no worries!
The kids will be fine now.
Guess they'll be able to
live normal lives, huh?
Yes.
It's unlikely the nations that abandoned
them will ever try to take them back.
That would violate international law, anyway.
They'd be making enemies of the
Free Union if they did that.
Are you going to give the kids IDs
and make them members of the Union?
Well, if that's what they want,
that might be a very good idea.
But for the time being, I'd like to
let them study at the Freedom Academy
and give them the chance
to choose their future.
Okay. I'm counting on you.
You needn't worry.
By the way, you still won't tell
me how you resolved all this?
That's a secret.
There are some things you don't need to know.
It's no substitute for telling you,
but I hope you'll be content with this...
Understood! Thank you, Master!
Hey, wait up!
So much has happened...
But now this case is closed.
All of our problems have been solved.
Shizu-san, this is for the best, right?
Thank you, Slime-san.
What a horrible blunder.
You finally summoned me,
and my own family got ahead of me.
Next time, without a doubt...
I know you will lead me to
the truth of this world.
Sensei... Sensei, don't go...
Chlo-chi... Don't try to keep Sensei here.
Yeah! Just get going already!
But...
Take care of them.
I will. You can count on me.
Sensei!
Jeez, Chloe, you're such a crybaby.
Stop crying!
You're crying, too, Ken-chan...
I'm not! My eyes are just sweating!
Sensei... Sensei...
Chloe.
There, there, Chloe.
I'll give you this, so cheer up, okay?
I wanted that, too!
But I got it.
Lucky!
No fair! No fair!
Oh, right. I have gifts for you guys, too.
Ken-chan, you look awesome!
So do you!
These are fantastic!
I-It's so cute!
There's a really handy girl
named Shuna in my country.
I had her make those and send them.
Sensei...
Thank you!
Now, listen. Be sure you study hard.
Saying goodbye is sad, but it's
not as if we'll never meet again.
I'll bring Ranga and come visit you.
Be sure to keep up with your studies,
even after we leave!
Y-You'd better come visit us!
Wh-When I graduate, I might
just come visit you, too!
Sure. I'll be waiting.
I'll have the entire city
of Rimuru welcome you.
Sensei!
See you again!
Take care!
Goodbye!
Be well!
See you again.
Master, why did you give
her your treasured mask?
Yeah, I wonder why, too...
I'm not sure either,
but for some reason, giving it to Chloe
felt like the natural thing to do.
Something told me that was best.
I see.
I bet Shizu-san would be happier
with Chloe having it than me.
She'll take good care of it.
She might even follow in Shizu-san's
footsteps to become a hero...
Heck, she might even become a Hero!
Surely not!
Ranga!
Yes, Master!
Let's go back to our town... to our home!
Everyone's waiting!
The man who thought he was living
a perfectly ordinary life
was stabbed by a random attacker and died,
and was reincarnated in another world.
He took in the Storm Dragon Veldora
as well as the will and
body of a certain girl,
overcame many crises,
brought together many races of monsters,
built a nation, and saved
a group of children.
His name is Rimuru Tempest,
and he is but a slime.
Next time, "Extra: Black and a Mask."
Extra: Black and a Mask