A city of monsters, home to a
slime that bested the Orc Lord...
Can this be true?
No, I know it's true.
I simply can't believe it.
But I have to believe it.
This slime called Rimuru has saved us.
True.
What sort of relationship
should we seek with them?
And should we do so on the assumption
that this slime is benevolent,
or should we perceive him as a threat
and attempt to eliminate him?
You speak of eliminating him so
easily, but is it even possible?
Shall I give you an honest answer?
I don't even need to hear it.
I suppose we should go and meet him once.
I will judge this Rimuru
with my own two eyes.
All right, let's move out.
We're going to go see
this slime you three met.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 17: The Gathering
This is delicious!
I love all the food in this town!
Give me more!
Were you okay yesterday?
Nothing to worry about! I—
...am quite tough, you know!
That's Sir Gabiru for you! So cool!
Did your communication crystal work okay?
Yes. I was able to contact King Gazel.
I informed him that the Demon Lord Milim
attacked and you dealt with her.
Good!
We'll just see how things
go with Milim for now.
Be sure to give me a report.
Of course.
This is Rimuru-sama's healing potion.
99% of its composition is
extracted from hipokute herbs.
Extracting...
Extraction
You can drink it or apply it on a wound!
The potion of total recovery: full potion!
In contrast, Dwarven techniques
can only extract up to 98%.
The potions we can make are "high potions."
A mere 1% makes a tremendous
difference in potency.
And now, at last,
I've overcome that 1% barrier!
This is the result of my research!
Oh? All right, I'll appraise it.
Please do.
Great Sage, use Appraisal.
Answer.
This potion is equal to a full potion.
Well done, Vesta!
It's definitely a full potion!
Excellent work, Vesta!
Assisting you in this endeavor
was truly worthwhile!
Way to go, Vesta!
I knew you were the right man
for this kind of research!
Thank you... Thank you.
Wow, I really didn't think
he'd be able to make it.
Now, if we move forward
with mass production...
I think if we sold this,
it'd be a great source of funds
for Tempest. What do you say?
I don't think that's gonna be easy.
This potion is too effective.
We can't rely on it for everyday use.
Fine quality like this
is best reserved for high-level heros
in life-or-death situations.
That's true.
The potions sold in the
Dwarven Kingdom are low potions,
which are mass-produced
by diluting high potions.
What do you say to
negotiating with King Gazel
to have those low potions
produced here in Tempest?
Hey, that could work!
If we produce and sell the potions here,
the Dwarven Kingdom would only need
to procure the necessary ingredients.
I get it. That would
benefit both nations, huh?
Okay. Let's bring that up for negotiation.
You guys can continue
with the production here.
Yes, sir!
What's going on?
A new guest arrived in town,
and Lady Milim took exception to him.
Let me through.
Rigurd, are you okay?
G-Rimuru-sama, it's you!
Huh?!
This is no cause for concern at all!
No way! That's serious!
This is who did that to you?
Correct.
Oh, Rimuru!
Yikes.
This guy thought he could mock us,
so I taught him a lesson!
I am one of Demon Lord
Carrion's Three Beastketeers,
Phobio the Black Leopard Fang.
I am the strongest warrior of
the Beast King's Beastketeers.
Nice town you've got here.
Fit to be ruled by the Beast King,
don't you think?
Surely you jest—
The Demon Lord Milim?!
Leopard Fang Flaming Palm!
What do you think you're doing
to my bestie's subordinate?!
I think she expects me to praise her.
And, um...
Should I really be praising her for this?
I doubt she'll get away with doing this to
an underling of this Demon Lord Carrion.
Didn't you promise not to cause any
commotion without my permission?
Huh?!
Er, well...
Y-Yeah! This is different!
He's not from this town, so it doesn't count!
It does count.
Huh?!
But since you did stand up for Rigurd,
I'll just make you go without lunch today.
That's cruel... That's too cruel!
This is all his fault!
This scumbag!
One hit wasn't enough!
At least give me one more—
Wait! Wait! Wait!
So, why did you come here?
Hmph. You expect me to answer a lowly slime?
You may call me "lowly,"
but I'm stronger than you.
I don't know this Demon Lord Carrion.
Depending on how you behave, my people
could become Carrion's enemies.
Do you want to be solely responsible for
antagonizing the entire Great Forest of Jura?
Hah! That's big talk.
This whole town is loyal to
a lowly monster like you?
Must be rough having nothing
but weaklings around.
Don't get a big head just because
Lady Milim took a liking to you.
Hey! Are you talking trash about my friend?
Milim, stop. If you do anything else,
you can kiss dinner goodbye.
Okay. I'll be quiet.
Now, it's true that I'm a slime.
But it's also a fact that
I rule 30% of this forest,
and if you're really serious, we may
have no choice but to declare war.
So think carefully before you answer me.
Lord Carrion ordered me to come here and
scout some mysterious majin to serve him.
Oh? He must mean us.
Looks like Milim wasn't the only
Demon Lord who had an eye on that battle.
Damn that Carrion! He broke his promise!
Well, I get the picture.
You can leave now.
Huh?
Rimuru-sama...
Are you sure about this?
Well, I can't kill him, can I?
Tell the Demon Lord Carrion
that if he wants to talk, he can
choose a date and contact us again.
I'll make you regret this.
Doesn't look like he'll
relay any message for us...
Okay, I want to know all about
this Demon Lord Carrion.
I can't tell you that.
We've sworn not to interfere with each other.
And there it is! She just confessed
that there's some secret!
Did you only make that promise with Carrion?
Or does it involve other Demon Lords, too?
Uh, that's...
Hey, it's okay!
Carrion used his underling to
interfere with you, didn't he?
And we're besties, so we
help each other out, right?
So I think it'd be a good idea for me
to know about the other Demon Lords.
If I don't know what kind
of promise you made,
I might end up interfering
without realizing it.
That's true...
But... Besties...
I know!
I'll make a weapon for you!
I'm concerned for you as
your bestie, after all!
A new weapon?!
Yeah, that's right!
Nothing's more important than your bestie!
Too easy. She's way too easy.
Demon Lords Clayman, Carrion, Frey,
and you, Milim, used Gelmud in a
scheme to create a puppet Demon Lord.
It was just a way to kill time.
Maybe that's all it was to you,
but since we butted in, I guess it's
inevitable that they'd target us.
It seems likely that other Demon
Lords will become involved, as well.
What a predicament...
We must consult with Lady Treyni.
It'll be fine!
Rimuru-sama has nothing to fear
from any of those Demon Lords!
Well, I've told you the secret.
Now give me my new weapon,
like you promised, bestie!
The storm that arose along
with Demon Lord Milim's attack
would gain strength along its path
to swallowing up Rimuru's
nation and his people.
One of the nations surrounding the Great
Forest of Jura, the Kingdom of Falmuth,
Barren Lands
The Western Provinces
The Eastern Plains
Tempest
is a major trade power known as the
gateway to the Western Provinces.
Kingdom of Ingrassia
Kingdom of Shiltrozzo
Kingdom of Falmuth
Kingdom of Blumund
Armed Nation
of Dwargon
Canaat Mountains
Sealed Cave
Lake Siss
It was from this kingdom
that a team was sent to the Forest
of Jura to learn about the Orc Lord.
Led by a man named Youm,
they're a rowdy gang,
brought together by money.
Captain of the Border Survey Corps  Youm
Boss—
Shh.
Whoa, this is bad!
But, but...
You guys... Whoa! Watch it!
Farsight
How have you three stayed alive
so long by being this careless?!
Sounds like some people
have encountered a monster.
What should we do, boss?
Hey! Wait for us!
Sorry to butt in!
We appreciate the help!
Sorry about this!
Here it comes!
A Knight Spider?!
All right, boys, assume formation.
Remove and heal anyone who gets hurt.
This is an order! Everyone stay alive!
Yeah!
Kajir, take command.
Got it.
Rommel, use a strengthening spell on me.
And you guys...
I'll make you pay for getting
us involved in this later.
Hey, Kaval! Is that you?
Good to see you again!
Gobta!
You're fighting monsters
every time I see you.
Do you enjoy fighting that much?
But I'll handle this one.
You're for dinner today!
You're kidding me...
These things are seriously
delicious, you know!
It'll be ready soon!
I can't wait!
I'm the representative of
this town... or nation...
called the Jura Tempest Federation.
My name's Rimuru Tempest.
You really are a slime!
By the way, Rimuru, there are some
folks here we didn't see last time.
Oh, yeah. This is Benimaru,
Shion, Souei, and Shuna.
And that's Milim.
So, the Kingdoms of Blumund and Falmuth
have both come to investigate this place?
We are—
Wait a minute.
Why is a slime acting like such a bigshot?
It makes no sense!
What's the deal here?
Why are all of you okay with this?
You are insulting Rimuru-sama.
Shut your mouth, Tits!
Boss!
Youm!
H-Hey...
I'm sorry!
Sorry about what Shion did.
She has trouble restraining
herself sometimes.
Cut her some slack.
That's mean! I'm actually
known for my patience!
You've got a long way to go if
you're that impatient, Shion!
You're so short-tempered because you
don't have an open mind like I do.
I want to be on good terms with Humans.
I hope we can trade and network
with you all someday, too.
Trade?
Yeah.
We've actually entered diplomatic relations
with the Dwarven Kingdom already.
With Dwargon?!
I think passing through this land would
be more convenient for your merchants.
What do you think?
Now, wait a minute!
You're saying that Dwargon acknowledges
this nation of monsters as legitimate?
I can vouch for that.
Minister Vesta!
Former minister.
What is a man of your standing doing here?
It's good to see you again, Fuze.
What Rimuru-sama says is true.
King Gazel and Rimuru have
entered into a treaty.
Are you convinced now?
W-Well... If that is the case, we aren't
opposed to cooperating with you.
But I'll need to see undeniable proof
that you are, in fact, an ally of Humans.
I assume that's all right?
Oh, sure. That's to be expected.
I'm just fine with that.
I'll permit you to stay here.
I want you to understand
that we aren't a threat.
By the way, Fuze-san,
has the news that the Orc Lord was
defeated already gotten around?
No, only our king and a select
handful of people know that.
I see. In that case...
Youm-kun, want to make a contract with me?
Huh? What are you even talki—
What... might you be suggesting?
You said the Kingdom of Falmuth
hired you with money, right?
So you'd just be switching employers.
To put it in simple terms...
I want you guys to be the heros
who defeated the Orc Lord.
What?!
Just say that we simply helped you out,
and start a rumor that you were
the one who defeated the Orc Lord.
I figure, that way,
I can be known as the trustworthy
monster who assisted the hero.
I think it'll be easier to
befriend people that way
than if they think I'm some
mysterious, threatening monster.
What do you say?
I get it.
Well put.
Have you gathered your thoughts?
Rimuru... No, Mr. Rimuru.
This town is really something.
After seeing all of them, I know
you're not some evil being.
We are people of guilty conscience.
We always longed to be free men.
We accepted the mission to come here
because we planned to make everyone
think we'd died on the way
and then head for some safe nation.
I've decided.
I'll trust you.
Allow me to call you
"Master Rimuru" from now on.
I am at your command.
Sure. I'll be counting on you.
Thus, Youm and his companions
began training under Hakurou
to look like heros.
That didn't take long.
You weren't noticed, were you, Tear?
I'm part of the Moderate Harlequin
Alliance, too, you know!
Have a little faith in me!
I'm just concerned you might go overboard.
Jeez! Stop treating me like a child already!
Very well.
I received word from Myulan.
It seems Milim has taken quite
a liking to those majin.
Huh...
This is turning out to be more
interesting than I expected.
How truly delightful.
Well, that's great,
but what's really going on?
Is this majin really so amazing that the
Demon Lord Milim would take interest?
Only to the point that we
mustn't simply ignore it.
He was no match for me, after all.
But then again, Laplace...
What about Laplace?
Shall we call it... an eeriness?
He says he felt something of that nature.
Oh, really?
If a cunning guy like Laplace said so,
maybe there really is something!
At the very least,
I think we should find out why the
Demon Lord Milim's taken such an interest.
Yes, we certainly will need to gather more
information and give it some thought.
Yeah, we should!
So, as for the results of my investigation!
Let's hear it.
Well, Frey apparently has no interest in
getting involved with the Forest of Jura.
She seemed wary of something.
It was almost as if she
was preparing for battle!
And did you find out the reason for that?
I did! You won't believe this!
She was freaking out, saying Charybdis
was going to be revived!
Charybdis?
I see.
Now, Tear, I have another
task I'd like you to handle.
I thought you would!
I've already called Footman,
so a little fighting is no problem!
That's wonderful, Tear.
But I would like you to avoid
violence as much as possible.
First, seek out the location of the seal
and find out whether or
not we can tame Charybdis.
Leave it to me, Clayman!
The location should be—
I said leave it to me!
Okay, I'm going now!
Charybdis, eh?
With power said to rival
that of the Demon Lords...
I truly look forward to
seeing what it is like.
Next time, "Evil Creeps Closer."
Evil Creeps Closer