Ruler of monsters, and all
those who are loyal to him,
forgive me for this unannounced visit.
I am Treyni, a Dryad.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
Rimuru Tempest, ruler of
monsters, I would like you
to defeat the Orc Lord.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 12: The Gears Spin Out of Control
Defeat the Orc Lord?
Um... You're asking me?
Yes, that's right.
That's quite a selfish request from
someone who just appeared out of nowhere,
Treyni the Dryad.
Why have you come here?
There are races far stronger than Goblins.
Yes, that is true.
If the Ogres' homeland had
been at full strength,
perhaps I would have gone there.
Though, even if I had done that,
I still could not have ignored
this individual's existence.
Were our settlement to be
attacked by the Orc Lord,
the Dryads could not hope
to fight them alone.
This is why I have come to request
assistance from someone strong.
The idea that the Orc Lord even existed
was still just a theory to us...
The Dryads have knowledge of essentially
everything that happens in this forest.
The Orc Lord does exist.
If a Dryad acknowledges it...
Then it must be true.
Give me some time to answer.
I will back up the Kijin,
but I don't want to go poking at
a hornet's nest for no reason.
Let me take stock of the information
we have before I answer.
Despite how I look, I'm the
leader here, after all.
Let's continue the conference.
Anyone have any ideas what
the Orcs might be after?
One thing does come to mind...
Okay.
Souei, did you investigate our village?
Yes.
Judging by your reaction,
I assume you found none?
Correct.
Not a single one belonging to
either our brethren or the Orcs.
Not one what?
Corpse.
We didn't understand how they
were getting the supplies
to keep an army of 200,000 fed.
Are you saying...
The unique skill...
Starved
Starved.
Starved?
It's a skill that the Orc Lord,
a calamity that brings chaos
to the world, is born with.
Its influence reaches all
those who serve under him,
Trample all! Trample all! Trample all!
making them devour everything
in sight, like locusts.
At the same time, they consume the
victim's strength and abilities,
making them their own sustenance.
The strength of this comrade
we eat is now ours!
The strength of this prey we eat is now ours!
It's quite similar to your Predator skill.
In return for obtaining Starved,
they feel constant, insatiable hunger.
The Orcs move forward for no other purpose
than to sate their endless
hunger and gain more power.
That is their king's only wish.
So the Orcs' goal isn't to wipe out
the superior forest races,
the Ogres and Lizardmen,
but to steal their powers?
Well, if that's the case,
I can't say we're in the clear.
We have Tempest Wolves,
Kijin, and Hobgoblins.
Flavors aside, they're all meals with
powers that the Orcs would kill for.
Aren't you forgetting the one meal
that would attract them the most?
Huh?
We have the strongest slime here, remember?
Where?
Huh?
In addition, we have confirmed
that a certain majin
is behind the Orc Lord's appearance.
I believe it is someone you
won't want to overlook.
A majin?
It is a subordinate of
a Demon Lord, after all.
They have knowledge of everything
that happens in the forest, huh?
This lady's shrewd.
Honored Rimuru Tempest.
I once again request that
you defeat the Orc Lord.
As the one who received the
Storm Dragon Veldora's protection,
subjugated the Direwolves,
and became the patron of the Kijin,
you are surely more than
a match for the Orc Lord.
What do you think, Great Sage?
Can I trust her?
Caretakers of the Forest
The Dryads are the caretakers
of the Great Forest of Jura.
Caretakers of the Forest
They are said to be the ones who
pass divine justice on villains
They pass divine justice
on villains and any who would
harm the forest
and any who would harm the forest.
Divine Justice
Divine justice, huh?
But there are 200,000 of them.
Of course he will!
That Orc Lord is no match for Rimuru-sama!
Oh, you agree with me, then?
Yes!
Are you kidding me?! Did she really just...
Fine. I'll accept this request
to beat the Demon Lord.
You're all in this with me.
Of course, Rimuru-sama!
That was our plan all along.
We believe in you, and we're
with you. That's all we need.
Exactly!
Let's show them how strong we are!
Yeah!
I acted all cool about it,
but what if we lose?
If we're taking on an army of 200,000 Orcs,
I feel like we should consider
an alliance with the Lizardmen,
but given the guy they
had representing them...
I am Gabiru!
The Guy
I'd really like to talk to someone
who'll actually listen...
Rimuru-sama.
Would you mind if I spoke personally
with the chieftain of the Lizardmen?
Souei? You can do that?
Yes.
Oh, my God, he's so confident!
What a dreamboat!
O-Okay, then.
We'll join forces with the
Lizardmen and attack the Orcs.
Yes, sir!
The battle will probably take place in the
marshlands inhabited by the Lizardmen.
The Lizardmen's cooperation will
be essential for this to work.
I'm counting on you, Souei.
It shall be done.
I hope their chieftain isn't
an idiot like Gabiru...
Sir Gabiru!
You're awake now?
Sir Gabiru...
Wh-Where are we?
Thank goodness...
Th-That's right! I was...
defeated by that boy with the dopey face!
They clearly tricked us.
What do you mean?
It's simple.
That boy who beat me
is obviously the real master of that village!
Really?!
That kid?
He must be, or Sir Gabiru wouldn't have lost!
Indeed.
What a dirty trick, lowering
Sir Gabiru's guard with such lies!
Cowards!
How dare they?!
Now, calm down.
Such is the wisdom of the weak.
What a great man you are!
Great as a mountain!
That's our Sir Gabiru!
Yeah! Our next chieftain!
You're the best, Gabiru!
Oh, no, I'm really not so—
Wait, who?! Wha?!
He's been here this whole time.
You're just as great as I've heard!
My name is Laplace.
Laplace?
I've come as a servant of
Lord Gelmud to give you a warning.
Oh! Lord Gelmud!
Who's Lord Gelmud?
He's the man who gave Sir Gabiru his name.
Thank you for taking the trouble to come!
So, what is Lord Gelmud's warning?
Well, we have quite the
situation on our hands!
It seems that army of Orcs
really is being led by an Orc Lord.
An Orc Lord?!
The Lizardman chieftain is a capable man,
but he's getting up there in years, you know!
Frankly speaking...
Don't you think this is a bit
much for Daddy to handle?
I had planned to take over as chieftain
after we had fought off the Orcs,
but it seems that would be too late!
Yep, exactly!
Laplace, forgive my leaving
so abruptly, but we—
Oh, it's fine, it's fine!
You're going back to the marshlands, right?
You should hurry!
Thank you.
Let us go!
Yeah!
Do the best you can, Gabiru.
Trample all! Trample all! Trample all!
Chieftain, what shall we do?
The Orc army is approaching.
What can we do but remain here?
We have no means to fight
an army of 200,000 Orcs.
Yes, sir.
Chieftain!
Chieftain! We have an intruder!
He demands an audience with you!
Very well. Bring him to me.
Chieftain, is this not dangerous?
You can feel this aura, as well?
Yes. This is no simple intruder.
With this one...
even a hundred of the strongest
Lizardmen would stand no chance.
Forgive me, but my hands are
rather tied at the moment.
I cannot spare any hospitality.
No need to trouble yourself.
I am only a messenger, here to convey
to you the words of my master.
And what is your message?
My master desires an alliance
with the Lizardmen.
An alliance?
But I have no knowledge of your master.
My master is the great Rimuru Tempest.
Upon receiving a personal
request from the Dryads,
he has sworn to defeat
the approaching Orc army.
A personal request from the
caretakers of the forest?
She informed us that the Orc
army is led by an Orc Lord.
An Orc Lord?!
Keep in mind what that means
as you consider our proposal.
Rimuru, you say? Never heard of him!
He probably just came crying to
us because he fears the Orc Lord!
If he would just ask for our help...
Enough.
Hold your tongue.
Ch-Chieftain! Such complacency
will lead others to belittle—
Wh-What is this?
Hold.
I apologize for my comrade's rudeness.
Would you please forgive him?
This offer does benefit both
of us equally, does it not?
Forgive me.
It was not my intent to threaten him,
but I will not stand for
such mockery of my master.
Strong words...
Had I not stopped him, he would have
taken his head in a heartbeat.
Judging by your aura, you appear
to be an Ogre from the southwest.
Not anymore.
My master granted me the name
"Souei," and I became a Kijin.
Kijin?
The superior race born only
rarely from among the Ogres?
If that is true, it would
mean that your master
is of an even more superior
race than the Kijin...
An offer to enter an alliance
immediately after the
appearance of the Orc Lord...
I have no reason to refuse.
However...
Souei, was it? I have one condition.
What is it?
I wish to meet your master, Rimuru Tempest.
Very well.
Then we will make preparations
and meet you here in seven days.
You will have an audience with him then.
Ensure that you do not
wage battle before then.
Understood.
Then I will go.
Chieftain!
I feel as if I've seen the light of hope.
Gather everyone together.
The Orc army has already drawn
near to this underground cave.
But there is nothing to fear.
In seven days,
powerful reinforcements will join us.
Until then, we will remain here and
conserve our strength for battle.
Do not, for a moment,
think of making the first strike.
Any who die in battle will be eaten by
the enemy and become their strength!
That is what it means to fight the Orc Lord.
Once our reinforcements join us,
we will launch a counterattack.
Resist fighting until then!
I will not tolerate a
single death among my men!
Four Days Later
All right! Surround him!
Is this really an Orc?
I feel like I just fought an Ogre...
It's chilling to think that there
are 200,000 of these guys.
That must be the power of the Orc Lord.
Can we defend this place for three more days?
If all we do is defend,
we'll exhaust our strength!
You're...
Father!
Ah, you've returned.
Well?
Did you succeed in recruiting
the Goblins to assist us?
Yes, sir!
They number 7,000 in total.
They are standing by.
But...
Why must we remain here in
the face of an Orc attack?
This is not how the proud
Lizardman race fights.
While you were away, we were
approached with an offer of alliance.
Until they join us, our best
option is to focus on defense.
You've aged, Father.
What?
Utilizing these natural labyrinths may
be a wise strategy against a large army.
However, it divides our forces
between too many separate corridors,
preventing us from meeting the
enemy with our full strength!
G-Gabiru, what is the meaning of this?
Be calm, captain of the guard.
I have no intention of harming you.
But...
I will apologize later for
resorting to violence.
You may feel uncomfortable while restrained,
but bear with it until I defeat the Orc Lord.
Son! I will not allow you to do this!
Gabiru... no, Brother!
Please, come to your senses!
Unhand me! Unhand me, I said!
Unhand me at once! I will not stand for this!
Sir Gabiru, here.
That's my father's...
Th-This power...
Vortex Spear, you acknowledge
me as your master now?
We've seized the leaders of each clan.
There were a lot of young ones who didn't
agree with this defensive battle.
I see.
We're all behind you.
We're counting on you, Sir Gabiru.
Of course.
I will show you how a true Lizardman fights!
The time has come!
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
Trample all! Trample all! Trample all!
The Orc army filled the marshlands.
From one corner of their ranks,
a commotion arose.
There is no need to fear these
pigs any more than before!
These marshlands are our domain!
We will throw the Orcs into
confusion with our agility!
We will not lose to these dimwits
whose feet are held by the mud!
All right!
Our attack is making a dent!
Indeed.
Mere Orcs are no match for us Lizardmen!
Right! Withdraw for now!
Gabiru's men had to acknowledge his talents.
What's happening?
If there was anything
they didn't account for,
it was that Gabiru didn't know...
the terror of the Orc Lord.
The Orcs... are eating other Orcs?
The chieftain did know the
terror of the Orc Lord.
This difference between
the two of them was now
bearing its fangs at Gabiru.
Trample all! Trample all! Trample all!
The strength of this comrade
we eat is now ours!
The strength of this prey we eat is now ours!
Next time, "The Great Clash."
The Great Clash