The day after the defeat
of the Demon Lord Geld,
representatives of each
race gathered together
to discuss what would
happen after the battle.
Chairman Rimuru Tempest,
please begin the conference.
Uh...
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 15: The Jura Forest Alliance
Uh... I've never led a meeting like this
before, so it's not my strong suit.
So I'll just say what's on my mind.
I'd like you to save your
deliberations until after that.
I'll start by saying this: I don't intend
to charge the Orcs with any crimes.
I know this may upset the Lizardmen,
who suffered the most casualties,
but hear me out.
The cause of all this was
starvation due to a famine.
Anyone, of any race, might have made
the same choices under those conditions.
Of course, this is just my
public stance on the matter.
Then may we hear your personal
thoughts on it, as well?
I've taken all of the Orcs' sins upon myself.
If anyone has a complaint, bring it to me.
P-Please, wait!
Surely there is no logic to—
That was my promise with the Demon Lord Geld.
I see.
However, I feel that answer
is somewhat unfair.
Yeah, I can see why he
wouldn't accept it so easily.
There is one immutable rule
shared among all monsters:
"Survival of the fittest."
The moment they faced each other,
they were both prepared for that.
You guys lost your home, too.
Don't you have any complaints?
I would be lying if I said we didn't,
but if it happens again, we will not
disgrace ourselves a second time.
Uh-huh...
I see... That is a fair point.
But there is one thing I must know.
What's that?
What will be done with the Orcs?
You have said you will not
charge them with any crimes.
Does that mean you intend to
accept all of their survivors?
Even with their numbers down,
there are still 150,000 of them.
That being the case...
It may sound like some kind of dream,
but I'm thinking we can all work together.
Work together?
Meaning what, exactly?
The Lizardmen will share a
clean water source and fish,
the Goblins will offer places to live,
and our town will give them processed goods.
And in return,
the Orcs will contribute labor.
All the races of the Great Forest
of Jura will form an alliance
and build a mutually
cooperative relationship.
It'd be really cool if we could create
a nation where all races could coexist!
A-And you're saying we could
also take part in this alliance?
Well, you have nowhere else to go, do you?
I have a place for you, so do some work.
I won't tolerate slackers.
Yes, sir!
Of course! Of course we will!
We will devote our lives to our work!
We would be honored to join forces with you.
Treyni-san, is that okay with you?
Certainly.
The Treants under my protection will
share the bounty of the forest, as well.
I believe we can alleviate the
Orcs' hunger for some time.
Then...
As a caretaker of the forest,
I, Treyni, hereby pledge
to acknowledge Rimuru-sama as the new
chancellor of the Great Forest of Jura...
Chancellor?!
...and declare the Jura Forest Alliance
to be established under Chancellor Rimuru.
Uh... Er... Buh...
S-Somehow I just ended up the
chancellor of the alliance...
Not Treyni-san?!
And declining really doesn't
seem like an option right now...
F-Fine, I will! I'll do it!
Okay, um... I guess that's how it's gonna be,
so I'm counting on all of you!
Yes, sir!
And thus, while I was left in
an uncontrollable cold sweat,
the Jura Forest Alliance was established.
You need something?
Even in the name of survival of the fittest,
hate is not a thing that
can be resolved so easily.
For what we did to your village...
I cannot apologize enough.
I realize this is a selfish request...
but please, take my head as penance
and have mercy on the others!
After the battle, we told Rimuru-sama
that we wished to continue serving him,
and he gave us official titles.
I am a Samurai, bodyguard to Rimuru-sama.
Samurai
I'm also his secretary.
Instructor
Spy
Hakurou is an Instructor, and Souei is a Spy.
Swordsmith
Holy
Princess
Shuna and Kurobe, who remained in
the village, have titles, as well.
And I received the title of Samurai General.
Samurai
General
That puts me in charge of military affairs.
And now that I'm in this position,
I can't very well rob us of a
capable fighter, now, can I?
I will show no mercy to any
who do wrong to Rimuru-sama,
but if you join the alliance and revere
him as your chancellor, we are not enemies.
I wouldn't dream of doing him wrong!
He saved all of us.
I wish only to serve him.
I could never bear him ill will!
Then we are fellow servants
under the same master.
Do your best to be useful to Rimuru-sama.
I'll accept that as your apology.
I swear on the name of my father King Geld.
Benimaru is such a gracious guy.
I should learn from him.
And I'll have to give that one a name,
as the new leader of the Orcs.
In hopes that you inherit the
wishes of the Orc Disaster, Geld,
I grant you the name "Geld."
Yes, sir!
Lead the Orcs well.
Yes, sir.
The new Orc ruler, Geld,
evolved into the Orc King.
After that...
I spent ten days naming all 150,000 Orcs.
It goes without saying that I
went into sleep mode after that.
I also gave the name "Abiru"
to the Lizardmen's chieftain.
His son, Gabiru,
was charged with the crime of treason.
I'm sure to receive the death penalty.
That's as it should be.
It's the only way to set an example.
But... if there's one thing I regret...
I wish I had asked him why he saved me.
A worthless fool like me...
Raise your head.
I will now state the verdict.
I will, at least, accept the
death penalty with grace.
Gabiru, you will be
excommunicated and exiled.
You will never call yourself
a Lizardman again.
Cast him out at once!
What... did he say?!
You forgot something.
Here.
Sir Gabiru!
Hey!
We've been waiting for you, Sir Gabiru!
We were getting sick of waiting!
Time is money.
Wh-What are you guys doing?!
I've been excommunicated!
If you're excommunicated,
we're all excommunicated!
Indeed.
You guys...
You're such fools.
Hopeless, every last one of you!
Very well. I'll look after all of you.
Just follow me!
That's our boy!
So cool!
Most definitely!
After you went to the trouble
of settin' all that up,
I bet it's killin' you that a
new Demon Lord wasn't born, huh?
Yes...
But I did get to see an interesting sight.
Now, what shall I do about that slime?
Well, good luck to ya.
If ya ever need a hand,
I'll lend ya one for cheap,
Demon Lord Clayman.
Three months after the
defeat of the Orc Lord,
the High Orcs that had evolved from the Orcs
were learning new skills in no time,
under Kaijin's instruction,
and had become a dependable work force.
It's great that the houses have been built.
We've got clothing and tools, too.
And...
We laid an aqueduct, too!
We even have flushing toilets,
and both water and sewage systems!
We're building roads, too.
The stuff I learned as a general
contractor came in handy!
This'll be great for commerce with
the Lizardmen and other regions.
The bath I asked for will
be finished soon, too.
I can't wait!
Right, Ranga?
We should all work hard together to make
this village an even greater place.
Yes, master! As you wish!
A place to live in peace...
At last, our town was complete!
But... things just couldn't be that easy.
Rimuru-sama, we have an emergency.
Huh?
Several hundred pegasus-mounted
knights are heading this way.
What?
Your Majesty, what news?
The Orc Lord has been defeated,
and the war has ended.
What?!
Rather than rampaging, the 150,000
surviving Orcs have scattered.
On top of that, they've evolved into High Orcs.
That can't be...
With the participation of several
superior majin, the war came to an end.
Is it safe to assume the majin
are all serving that slime?
One who rules over majin and
causes monsters to evolve...
If this matter is not handled
with care, this nation may fall.
I will see just who this
slime is with my own eyes.
It can't be...
The Hero King of the Dwarves,
Gazel Dwargo...
Rimuru-sama, what shall we do?
I'd rather avoid fighting if possible...
It's no problem.
We can just knock them all away.
If it comes down to a fight,
evacuate the townsfolk.
We'll buy time until then.
Right.
It is a pleasure to see you again.
It's been a long time, Kaijin.
Yes, Majesty!
You are the slime?
I'll introduce myself first.
My name is Rimuru.
I'm a slime, but I'd rather
you didn't call me that.
I am the chancellor of the
Jura Forest Alliance, after all.
This isn't really my true form,
but it's easier to talk to me this way, right?
So... why are you here?
I'll get right to the point.
Rimuru, I've come to see what you truly are.
What I truly—
I will expose your true nature with my sword!
Since you boasted of being
the chancellor of this forest,
it seems I must teach you,
exactly, where you stand!
If that sword is more than mere decoration,
you would do well to accept my proposal.
Your Majesty, are you...
An earnest battle is the quickest
way to settle this, is it not?
All right, then. I accept.
I'll make you regret accusing me of boasting.
If you can defend against my
entire chain of attacks, you win.
However...
I suggest you do not underestimate the
sword skill of Master Swordsman Gazel Dwargo.
Fine.
Very well. I will serve as
witness to this contest.
Is that... a Dryad?
I willingly apologize for
accusing you of boasting.
I have a vague understanding
of the circumstances now.
Then...
But that is a separate matter
from judging your true nature.
Huh?
Now that we have a witness,
all that remains is to cross swords!
Yeah, I guess so.
I'll win this in no time and make
you explain what's going on here.
If you manage to defeat me,
you will have your answer.
Begin!
Is that all the strength you have, Rimuru?
Quiet! I just haven't started
taking this seriously yet.
Don't rush me.
He's strong, all right...
But I can't just lose this.
That stance...
Here I come, Rimuru!
Haze: Thunder of Heaven and Earth
Haze: Thunder of Heaven and Earth!
The next strike is coming... from above!
You managed to stop my strike!
Enough.
The winner is Rimuru Tempest.
I understand now after
crossing swords with you.
You are not an evil being.
What the hell?
I am impressed that you saw through
my Haze: Thunder of Heaven and Earth.
Well done, Rimuru.
Oh, that was just a coincidence.
My master used that move, so I
dealt with it a lot in training.
That's all, really.
What? Could it be your master was...
Excellent work, Rimuru-sama.
The Savant!
You no longer look like the little
boy I found lost in the forest.
Ah... Forgive me, Dwarf King.
I am overjoyed to see that you
have surpassed me with the sword.
What an honor to hear you say that.
Hakurou was his master, huh?
You really never can tell how things
might be connected in this world.
Rimuru-sama really is amazing, huh?
Truly the best.
I see.
You were investigating the odd assembly
of monsters that defeated the Orc Lord.
Yes, to determine whether
they were friend or foe.
Rimuru, there's something I must ask you.
Sure.
Have you any interest in
entering a treaty with me?
If you were to gain control of
everything in this vast forest,
you could obtain wealth and
power surpassing my own nation.
It would serve you well to have another
nation supporting you at such a time.
That would be fantastic, but...
Are you sure?
That would be the same as acknowledging our
gathering of monsters as its own nation.
Of course.
And this deal would benefit us, as well.
Both sides stand to profit.
I guess I have no reason to refuse.
I gladly accept.
Good.
And what is the name of your nation?
Our nation's name?
I didn't think of that!
Um... If I take one from "Forest
of Jura" and "Rimuru Tempest"...
The Jura Tempest Federation!
The Jura Tempest Federation?
That's our Rimuru-sama!
Then our nation shall be called
the Jura Tempest Federation,
and this town shall be called Rimuru!
Huh?!
Capital City Rimuru!
Hang on, that's kinda embarrassi—
No other name would do!
I agree. It's a perfect name for our town.
H-Huh?
It would seem that this is settled.
Yeah.
On this day, the names "the Jura Tempest
Federation" and "Capital City Rimuru"
were engraved in history for the first time.
Next time, "Demon Lord Milim Attacks."
Demon Lord Milim Attacks