That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 10: The Orc Lord
G-Rimuru-sama?
Is it not to your tastes?
That's so good!
This is bliss!
I didn't have a sense of
taste in my slime form.
This is the first time I've tasted
food since I came to this world.
It's so great to be alive!
The Orcs attacked the Ogres?
That can't be!
It's the truth.
Can such a thing really happen?
I don't know.
Is it that strange?
Gobta...
Of course it is.
Ogres are immeasurably stronger than Orcs.
That such a weak race would
attack them is unthinkable.
Nevertheless, they did come.
They attacked our village out of nowhere.
They carried weapons and wore armor,
and their overwhelming numbers
filled the entire forest.
Those detestable pigs...
overran our village.
Orcs wearing armor?
Yes, the same type of full
plate mail that Humans wear.
That must mean...
It's likely the Orcs are not working alone.
Orcs could never round up all
that valuable armor themselves.
Exactly.
Among them was...
A masked majin?
It was a high-level majin.
I'm certain of it.
And you fought Rimuru-sama because
you had mistaken him for this masked majin.
Yes.
So... what does all this mean?
That the Orcs have sided with one
of the Demon Lords, possibly?
I see... I guess?
A Demon Lord, eh?
But why a Demon Lord?
I don't know.
The only thing I'm sure of is that
only six of my three hundred
brethren remain alive.
I see.
No wonder you're upset.
Have you had enough meat, Rimuru?
I'm taking a break.
Your little sister's really something.
She knows a lot about
medicinal and cooking herbs.
The Goblins took to her immediately.
She was a sheltered child.
She must be happy that
they're relying on her.
So, what are you guys going to do now?
What do you mean?
I mean your plans for the future.
Whether you rebuild your village
or relocate to another area,
the fate of your comrades is depending
on your leadership, right?
That's easy.
We will build our strength
and take them on again.
Do you know where to find them?
He doesn't have a plan at all.
Well, I have a suggestion.
Do you guys have any interest
in being my subordinates?
Subordinates?
Of course, all I can pay you
is guaranteed food, shelter, and clothing.
You need a home base, right?
But that would involve your
whole village in our revenge.
Well... I'm not just offering
this as a favor to you guys.
You said thousands of armed
Orcs attacked you, right?
And there might be a
Demon Lord pulling the strings.
The Orcs may be seeking dominion
over the Great Forest of Jura.
This town isn't completely safe, either.
Which is why adding as many to our
numbers as possible would benefit us.
Plus, if anything happened to
you guys, I'd fight with you.
I'll never abandon a friend.
I see.
Let me give it some thought.
Sure. Take all the time you
need to think about it.
Well, I think I'll go get some more meat.
It's not a bad offer.
But it's your choice to make.
We'll do whatever you
and the princess decide.
If only I were stronger...
Have you decided?
The Ogres are a warring clan.
We aren't against taking to the
battlefield in service to another.
If our master is strong, we are
all the more pleased to serve them.
Can our contract last only until
we take out the Orcs' leader?
You can do whatever you want after that.
You can stay and help us build a nation,
or you can go on your way.
I would like to accept the
offer you presented last night.
We will hereby serve under you.
Good.
I should've given more
consideration to how he feels.
I'm sure all he wants is
to avenge his people now,
even if it gets him killed.
He's making this decision as a leader
who's had to accept his own weakness.
Lift your head.
You're all accepted. Call in the others.
Yes, sir.
All I can do...
is make sure he won't regret that decision.
I'll give you names to prove
you're my subordinates.
All of us?
Well, having no name makes
things tough, doesn't it?
But...
P-Please, wait.
Giving a name comes with great risks.
And to name such superior monsters—
It's fine, really. Don't worry about it.
But...
The "risk" is me using too many
magicules and falling asleep, right?
There's only six of them
this time, so it'll be fine.
Or do you just not want me to name you?
That isn't...
We have no complaints.
Brother!
We gratefully accept your names.
If this is the young master's will, we accept.
Okay, let's get started.
You are...
Shion, it's time to switch places.
Oh, no, Princess.
I will look after Rimuru-sama.
Please get some rest.
Really, Shion...
Rimuru-sama, good morning!
Um... Who are you again?
Wait... My memory's a little fuzzy,
but I think I was about
to name the Ogres when...
Huh?
Have you awakened, Rimuru-sama?
You're the "young master"
of the Ogres, right?
Correct.
I have evolved into a Kijin,
and I have assumed the name
you gave me: Benimaru.
Oh!
I remember now! I went into sleep
mode the moment I named him!
Wait, what did he say? "Kijin"? Not "Ogre"?
Kijin
"Kijin" refers to a race of
beings uncommonly born of Ogres.
beings uncommonly born of Ogres
Huh...
His body looks... a little smaller?
The amount of magicules in
him has exploded, though...
Is this a repeat of the Rigurd shock?!
This means he evolved from
an Ogre to a Kijin, right?
Rimuru-sama, I am Shuna.
I'm so glad to see that you've awakened.
Shuna...
Right, she's the Ogre princess.
She was already cute,
but she's even prettier now!
I am Shion.
I'm very fond of the name
you gave me, Rimuru-sama.
This busty beauty is Shion?
She looks less wild and more intelligent now.
And the one behind Benimaru...
is the old man who cut off my arm.
Such a mean-spirited remark.
It was I who felt shocked when you
instantly regenerated your arm.
He looks a lot younger now.
Is that a result of his evolution to Kijin?
And I think you're...
You have given me the name "Souei."
I am glad to see that you
have recovered, Rimuru-sama.
Th-Thanks.
Giving a name to a superior monster
consumes an equally large
amount of magicules.
In other words, naming just six of
them drained almost all my magicules?
I wish you'd told me that sooner.
Where's the sixth one?
Oh, he's been spending a lot
of time at Kaijin's workshop.
I heard Rimuru-sama has awakened!
Ah, there he is.
I think he looked like this.
I wonder how he changed...
Rimuru-sama!
I'm so glad you're well!
You recognize me, right? I am Kurobe.
He looks like an ordinary middle-aged guy!
So after a hot guy,
a cute girl,
a babe,
a dignified gray,
and another hot guy...
He's just a middle-aged guy! What a relief!
I hope we'll be good friends, Kurobe!
Sure!
Meanwhile...
The changes occurring in
the Great Forest of Jura
continued their invasive progress.
In the middle of the Great
Forest of Jura is Lake Siss.
Lake Siss
Vast marshlands surround the lake.
The Lizardmen control this territory.
R-Reporting!
We have spotted an Orc
army south of Lake Siss!
We believe they intend
to invade our territory!
Orcs?
Prepare for battle.
We'll beat those pigs senseless.
How many are there?
Well...
The Orc army numbers...
approximately 200,000.
I-Impossible! How can they
have twice what we have?!
We verified the number several times
with Magic Sense and Sense Heat Source.
I swear on my life that it is true.
Good work.
You may rest.
Yes, sir.
200,000?
How does one keep such a ridiculous
number of Orc bellies full?
They're supposed to be an uncoordinated
lot that does whatever they please.
No one could lead an outrageous
number like 200,000 of them!
I heard a rumor that they
destroyed the Ogre village.
They did what?!
The Orc Lord...
If there is an Orc who could command
a force of 200,000 of his brethren,
it would have to be the unique
monster of legend, the Orc Lord.
O-Orc Lord?
But that's...
No, if that really is true,
it would explain how he's able to
command such a huge army of Orcs.
But what would he want?
That doesn't matter!
The question is whether
or not we can defeat them!
If an Orc Lord truly has been born,
it will be difficult for us to win.
The Orc Lord is a true monster that devours
even the fear and terror of his own allies.
It is only a possibility,
but we must do everything we can possibly do.
And what does that entail?
I suppose we should request backup.
My son!
Is my son here?
I'm right here.
But, Father, must you address
me in such a boorish manner?
I have a name, Gabiru, which
was given to me by Lord Gelmud.
Gabiru
What you are called makes no difference.
There is something I need you to do.
What would that be?
You'll have to do better than that!
Well, come on! Strike back!
Gobta casually said he wanted to learn
swordsmanship, and this happened.
Hakurou is definitely a tough coach.
Orc Lord? What's that?
Well, put simply... it's a beast.
That's simple, all right.
It's said that one is born to
the Orcs every few centuries.
It's a unique monster.
Unique, huh?
They say he devours even his
own allies' fear and terror,
which makes him an
unnaturally effective leader.
Yikes.
The Orcs that attacked our village were
unfazed by the deaths of their own,
so I thought that may be the case.
I see.
Of course, the possibility
of it is quite low.
Any other ideas why they might
have attacked your village?
Well...
I'm not sure if there's any connection,
but shortly before the attack,
a majin visited our village...
I shall name you.
He said that, but he
sounded too untrustworthy,
so I turned him away,
and he cursed me as he left.
A majin, huh?
So you think he might have
a grudge against you?
I had no other choice.
I want no such gift from
an unsuitable master.
I wouldn't accept a name
from just anyone, after all.
What was his name again?
I think he said...
Gela... Geli... Gele... Gelo?
Gelmud.
Right, that's it.
Gelmud? I think I've
heard that name before...
Rigur-kun, who gave your brother his name?
Sir! I'm told he received his name from
a passing Demon called Lord Gelmud.
He saw promise in him.
Gel...?
Gelmud. He's an officer
in the Demon Lord's army.
I bet it's the same guy.
Does he just go around naming whoever?
Why?
I bring a report, Rimuru-sama.
Okay.
I witnessed a group of Lizardmen.
Lizardmen? Not Orcs?
Correct.
Because they make the marshlands their home,
it seemed unnatural to see them near here,
so I had to inform you at once.
They seemed to be attempting negotiations
with a nearby Goblin village.
They may one day come here, as well.
I see...
Lizardmen...
Honestly, that father of mine...
Visit the local Goblin villages
and enlist their aid.
Indeed!
It is not the way of the proud
Lizardman race to fear mere Orcs!
And he used to be such a great man...
Hey, Sir Gabiru, when are you
gonna become the chieftain?
Oh, no. My comment may have
been a bit disrespectful,
but I still fall far short of my father.
Really?
But as you are now, I bet you're just as
mighty as the chieftain during his glory days!
I agree.
No, really, I...
I mean, you're named, after all!
Yes, and you are unequaled
in the art of the spear.
If you don't take your
stand now, when will you?
Eh? What is this?
Could it be... that I'm
actually pretty great?!
You are right.
My father has grown old.
Even if I must be a bit forceful,
I will show him that I have
strength worthy of a chieftain!
Then he can retire with peace of mind.
You mean...
Yes!
Once I drive away the Orc army,
I will take my place as the
next Lizardman chieftain!
That's our Sir Gabiru! Woohoo!
You're on fire!
You will surely be chieftain!
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
Let's go!
Follow me, men! Your future is bright!
Gabiru! Gabiru! Gabiru!
Next time, "Gabiru Is Here!"
Gabiru Is Here!