That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
So, what do we do?
Episode 2: Meeting the Goblins
Hmm?
About the Unlimited Imprisonment
seal that hero put on you.
I feel bad knowing my friend's
been sealed here for 300 years.
You...
Don't give me those puppy dog eyes!
It'd be one thing coming from
a cute girl, but a dragon?
If you have a way to get
me out, I'd appreciate it.
Th-The thing is...
I wouldn't have lasted another 100
years before my magic ran out.
I keep losing more and more magicules...
So that's why this cave
is so rich in magicules,
and there are so many
valuable herbs and ore.
What happens when your magic runs out?
It's not a huge deal.
It's not?
I'll just die, that's all.
I... I see...
After all these years of
isolation, you just die, huh?
Might as well try this.
Great Sage, use Predator to consume
the Unlimited Imprisonment.
Failed.
I guess it won't be that easy.
See? It's impossible.
Isn't there anything we can do?
Examining the possibilities.
Hey! Don't just keep
talking to your own skill!
Old man...
Examination completed.
Possibilities include...
Uh-huh.
I see, I see.
It's only a possibility, but...
She says if we can analyze the Unlimited
Imprisonment from both inside and out,
we might be able to remove it.
Oh?
Wait, but... I can't analyze
it from the inside.
My skills are sealed along with me,
so I can't use them.
If you can just give me the data,
I can analyze it out here.
But that could take some time.
Are you sure you want to
stay in here that long?
W-Well, not that I mind, but...
Good point...
Since I'm here, I'd like to search
for others from my homeland.
I see...
So here's a suggestion.
A suggestion?
Want to get in my stomach?
I'll use my skills, Great Sage and Predator,
to analyze Unlimited Imprisonment
while you try to destroy it from the inside.
You'll be quarantined in my
stomach, so you won't disappear.
What do you say?
That sounds interesting! Please, do it!
I'll entrust my entirety to you!
Are you sure you want to
believe me that easily?
Of course!
It sounds more fun to break through
Unlimited Imprisonment together
than to wait here alone until you come back!
Right...
Better two than one...
Sounds great!
Yes!
O-Okay, I'll use Predator to—
W-Wait a moment!
Before we start, I'll give you a name.
You can give me one, too.
Huh?
It will engrave onto our souls
the fact that we are equals.
It'll be what humans call a "family name,"
but the name I give you will
grant you divine protection.
You are still nameless, so you'll
become a monster with a name.
A monster with a name, huh?
That sounds good!
Doesn't it?
Give me a cool name!
Same to you!
A cool name...
Let's see...
The Storm Dragon, Veldora...
Storm, huh?
And... what's another
word for a storm, again?
Storm... sounds kinda weird.
Tempest!
What do you think of "Tempest"?
What?!
Tempest, you say?!
D-Don't like it?
It sounds fantastic!
As of today, I am Veldora Tempest!
Y-You like it?
And I will grant you the name "Rimuru."
Rimuru...
Not bad.
You will be Rimuru Tempest!
At that moment, something
changed deep in my soul.
Rimuru Tempest
The name "Rimuru Tempest"
had become engraved upon it.
I am... Rimuru Tempest.
Rimuru...
Veldora Tempest...
Okay, I'm going to eat you now.
Break out of that
Unlimited Imprisonment already!
Leave it to me.
I will see you face-to-face in no time!
All right!
Unique skill: Predator!
That ended far too soon.
I was just talking with him a moment ago...
Unlimited Imprisonment
Would you like to analyze the unique
skill Unlimited Imprisonment?
Yes. Please do it.
A great tremor rocked the world on this day.
The disappearance of the
Storm Dragon Veldora,
a Catastrophe-class monster, was confirmed.
The cave where Veldora had been sealed
was in the Great Forest of Jura.
In the area of the Great Forest
of Jura are several countries.
Barren Lands
The Western Provinces
The Eastern Plains
Great Forest of Jura
Canaat Mountains
Kingdom of Falmus
Kingdom of Blumund
Sealed Cave
Lake Siss
In one of them, the Kingdom of Blumund...
Kingdom of Blumund
Minister Baron Veryard
You've heard about the
Storm Dragon Veldora, yes?
Of course I have.
Guild Master Fuze
I should have expected
as much of a guild master.
So, can you tell me what measures
the guild intends to take?
We have no plans to take
any particular action.
The disappearance of Veldora is predicted
to galvanize the monsters!
There is a chance that the Eastern
Kingdom will advance through the
previously impassable region that
the Storm Dragon was sealed in.
If they get through that forest,
the provinces surrounding
the Great Forest of Jura
will fall under the empire's
rule, in the blink of an eye.
You look tired.
Are you getting enough sleep?
As a favor to an old friend,
I'll conduct an investigation personally.
I'll look into the state of the Great Forest
of Jura and the kingdom's movements.
Thank you. Please see to it.
The chaos in the surrounding
countries since noticing
that Veldora disappeared was
like a disturbed hornet's nest.
Of course, Rimuru had no way to know this.
How many days has it been
since I ate Veldora?
I wandered around everywhere,
trying to get out of the cave.
I gobbled up all the herbs
and ores I came across
to store them in my body.
Water Movement
Skill: Water Movement acquired.
Acquired
— Water Blade  —
Skill: Water Blade acquired.
The acquired skills Water Pressure Propulsion,
Water Movement, and Water Blade
Water Pressure
Propulsion
Water Movement
Water Blade
Water Pressure
Propulsion
Water Movement
Water Blade
Water Pressure
Propulsion
Water Movement
Combine
combine to evolve into extra
skill, Water Manipulation.
Water Manipulation
Evolution
I tried out lots of things
and gained some new skills.
And then... I found the one!
The one bound to me by
the red thread of fate!
Except it wasn't.
Black Serpent Appeared
This looks bad.
I doubt it's gonna let me escape.
But wait... This is nothing
compared to Veldora, is it?
Maybe it's not as scary as I thought.
I can do it!
Water Blade!
That's a much stronger
technique than I expected.
I'll have to be careful who I use it on...
Wait...
If I use Predator to eat
this snake and analyze it,
wouldn't I be able to take its abilities?
Right! Eat it whole!
Blech!
I can't taste things, but still! Blech!
Analysis complete.
Skills: Poisonous Breath and
Sense Heat Source acquired.
Poisonous
Breath
Sense
Heat Source
Poisonous
Breath
Acquired
Sense
Heat Source
Acquired
You can now mimic Black Serpent.
So I can breathe poison
and sense heat sources?
That could come in pretty handy.
Man, Predator sure is useful!
All right! I'm gonna
acquire a lot more skills!
Armorsaurus Appeared
Mimic Black Serpent
Take this!
— Poisonous Breath —
"Body Armor" Acquired
I'd better not use Poisonous
Breath anymore...
Evil Centipede Appeared
"Paralysis Breath" Acquired
Black Spider Appeared
Water Blade! Water Blade!
"Sticky Thread," and  "Steel Thread" Acquired
Giant Bat Appeared
"Drain," and "Ultrasonic Wave" Acquired
A red water strider, A-I-U-E-O!
Little shrimp swim in the algae!
Using the organ that the bat
used for its Ultrasonic Wave,
I was finally able to speak.
We are aliens.
Then, after several weeks of
wandering around that cave...
At last...
This is probably the exit, right?
Well, now what?
Can I cut it up with Water Blade?
It finally opened.
It's so rusty, the keyhole's falling apart.
That's no surprise.
Nobody's come in here for 300 years.
We won't be attacked out of nowhere, right?
Of course, if it comes to it,
we can always use Escape...
The first humans I've seen...
I don't know what they're here for,
but I guess they're adventurers?
Wait, I can understand them!
Intention
Magic Sense
The use of Magic Sense turns sound waves
that carry intention into comprehensible words.
Answer.
The use of Magic Sense turns sound waves
that carry intention into comprehensible words.
So that's why. Thank goodness!
I was never good at English.
And by producing sound waves that
carry your thoughts, you can converse.
Oh!
But I'm a slime now.
It would suck if I talked to them
and they immediately attacked me.
All right, I'm gonna
activate my Stealth Arts.
He called that skill "Stealth"?
You could peep all you wanted with that.
What a disgraceful creep!
I'll have to make friends with him later!
Are they gone?
What is it?
I thought I sensed a monster...
Was it my imagination?
So I left the cave.
How long has it been since
I walked in the sunlight?
There's been no sign of Veldora since then.
It seems like he vanished for good,
but I know that's not true.
I promised, after all.
I'll have to build up a lot of funny stories
to tell him about next time we meet.
Ah, I haven't seen the outside in so long!
The air tastes so sweet!
Not that I can taste.
Goblins Appeared
Hey, Veldora...
It looks like I'm about to have one funny
story to tell you about already.
Scrawny bodies,
beat-up weapons...
Strong one, do you have business here?
Strong one?
Wait, me?
I just need to produce sound
waves carrying my thoughts?
Okay!
Right, so, hello!
I'm a slime, and my name is Rimuru!
We're well aware of how strong you are, sir!
Please, quiet your voice!
Maybe I thought too hard...
So, did you need something?
We sensed a powerful monster,
so we came here as a precaution.
I don't sense anything like that.
Surely you jest!
Even if you face us in that
form, we won't be fooled!
I guess he really does mean me.
Strong one, having seen your
power, we wish to ask a favor.
Then I was led to the Goblin Village.
It sure is a shoddy village, though.
I bet Veldora could blow
it away with one snort.
Welcome, visitor.
I am the elder of this village.
Hi, nice to meet you.
So, what favor did you want to ask of me?
Have you noticed that monsters
have been unusually active of late?
No...
Our god disappeared one month ago.
As a result, monsters in the area
have been continually harassing us.
Their god? Does he mean Veldora?
The timing fits.
I guess he was keeping monsters away?
We tried to fight them,
but we lack the numbers...
S-So we hoped you would...
...help you out, huh?
But I'm just a slime.
I doubt I can do all the
things you expect of me.
Please, don't be modest.
Don't be modest.
A mere slime would not
emit such an intense aura.
You are quite a famous monster, are you not?
Aura?
What's he talking about?
I don't have one of those.
Great Sage, change Magic Sense's perspective
and let me look at myself.
Changing perspective.
Whoa! I've been emitting
an aura this whole time!
I feel like I've been walking down
a major street with my fly open!
This is bad!
So that's why the Goblins were scared of me!
Leave it to the elder to notice.
But of course. You cannot hide
the formidable air about you.
I see...
So you figured it out.
You guys show a lot of potential.
Oh, I sucked it in.
Ah... Have you been testing us?
It's fortunate that so many of
us were frightened by your aura.
Y-Yeah, that's right!
You've got potential if you
can talk to me without fear!
What potential?!
Come to think of it, how did those
humans in the cave not see my aura?
Are those guys okay?
Thank you so much.
Ah, as for the favor we wish to ask...
According to the Goblins,
wolf monsters, Direwolves,
attacked them from the east,
and many Goblins died in the ensuing battle.
Apparently, Direwolves are so much
more powerful than Goblins that
it takes ten Goblins to even have
a chance at beating one Direwolf.
And there was one warrior among them with
a name, who served as their guardian.
Even that warrior was killed,
leaving the village in peril.
There are about 100 Direwolves in total.
How many do we have?
Including females, we have
about 60 who can fight.
That's a pretty devastating
difference in strength.
It's like an impossible video game.
So did that Goblin warrior fight
them knowing he couldn't win?
No... That warrior gave
his life just retrieving
information on the Direwolves for us.
The warrior was my son,
and his elder brother.
I see...
Forgive me for asking that.
Elder, tell me one thing.
Y-Yes?
What will I get in return
for helping this village?
What can you guys give me?
I'm not actually looking for compensation.
I just need to put on a bit of a show.
W-We will offer you our loyalty!
Please grant us your protection!
If you do, we will swear our loyalty to you!
We will swear!
This looks familiar.
Senpai! Just this once, please!
Oh, all right.
When all is said and done,
I just can't say no.
Th-The Direwolves!
This is terrible!
We're done for!
We'll all be eaten!
Let's run!
B-But where?
E-Everyone, please calm down.
There's no need to fear.
We're going to defeat them.
Y-You mean...
In lieu of the Storm Dragon Veldora,
I, Rimuru Tempest, will grant your wish!
Thank you so much!
We are your loyal servants, great Rimuru!
You can count on me.
And that's how I became the Goblins' leader,
their guardian.
Next time, "Battle at the Goblin Village."
Battle at the Goblin Village