That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 20: Yuuki Kagurazaka
Now, do it!
Yes, sir!
Amazing! You're the best, Master!
One neatly filleted Megalodon!
A task simple enough to achieve before
breakfast... or dinner, in this case.
It's so light...
And so hard.
I bet we could use this.
It'll make some nice weapons.
It could be a shield, too.
Or we could even work it into some armor.
We could even make some
simple accessories with it.
They'd fetch a high price for sure.
Geld, that was some splendid fighting!
Your courage set an example
I'd like to follow!
You were unstoppable yourself, Gabiru!
I can't express my admiration enough!
Oh, no, Geld!
Oh, no, Gabiru!
You're both awesome!
With Charybdis no longer a threat,
peace returned to the city of Rimuru.
As an added windfall, the Demon Lord
Carrion agreed to a non-aggression pact,
adding further stability to the foundation
of the Jura Tempest Federation.
Sheesh... I'm really worn out after all this.
You were a big help, Milim. Thanks again.
It was nothing! It's only
natural I'd do that much!
Feel free to thank me more!
You were really something yourself, Rimuru!
If you said you planned to become a
Demon Lord, I'd have no objections!
A Demon Lord? You know I
wouldn't become one of those.
Is there any merit to being one?
Merit?
Why did you become a Demon Lord?
Why did I?
Did something bad happen and make
me become one out of frustration?
Uh, why are you asking me?
Good point! I can't really remember!
It was so long ago that I forgot!
I see.
Oh, yeah!
I just thought of one merit!
It's because I became a Demon Lord
that I found myself a bestie!
R-Right...
Anyway, bestie, I need
to get back to work now.
Work?
Right now?
That came out of nowhere.
Well, it doesn't mean
I'll never see you again!
We'll only be apart for a little while!
Transform!
I'll be sure to tell the other Demon Lords
not to mess with this place,
so don't worry about that!
You're going to see the other Demon Lords?
Indeed. That's my job!
Careful you don't let them trick you.
Please don't let them trick you.
Don't let them trick you.
Don't let them trick you, okay?
Make certain they do not trick you.
You all worry too much!
They can't trick me! I'm too smart!
Well, I'm off! Fwoosh!
Hey, wait!
Oh. She's gone.
I envy how free-spirited she is.
That's so very like Lady Milim, though.
I look forward to seeing her again.
Please... save... those children...
Hurry... to the royal capital...
Huh?
That... wasn't just a dream.
It's the regret Shizu-san's
clinging to, isn't it?
So I retired and became an instructor.
An instructor?
A teacher at a school.
Oh! There are schools here?
Yes, in a place called
the Kingdom of Ingrassia.
It was a school for kids from other worlds.
The royal capital of the Kingdom
of Ingrassia, huh?
There's Benimaru...
Kaijin...
Rigur...
The Goblin riders...
Geld...
Rigurd...
And heck, even Gabiru.
They should be just fine
without me for a while.
So that's why I'm planning to
go to the Kingdom of Ingrassia.
Those kids were one of the reasons
why Shizu-san made up her mind
to go see the Demon Lord Leon.
And I promised Shizu-san, after all.
I understand what you're saying... but...
If anything should happen to you,
the Jura Forest Alliance could
be ripped up from its very roots,
after it was only just
beginning to come together.
I will go with him.
You can all rest at ease.
What Ranga said.
Work together to keep this town safe.
I need you all to fulfill
your roles the best you can.
Yes, sir!
Well, I'm off.
P-Please, be well! We will
await your return always!
Sir Gabiru, you're so sensitive!
Sir Gabiru, you're so kind!
Don't be so dramatic.
I'll be back in no time.
Please do come back as soon as you can!
I pray you'll have a safe journey.
Later!
Farewell!
And so, I was on my way.
In the two years since I reincarnated here,
it's my first time visiting
a nation of humans,
so I'm a little excited.
Holy Empire
Ruberios
Kingdom of Ingrassia
The Western Provinces
Sorcerer's Dynasty Sarion
The Kingdom of Ingrassia lies
to the west of our nation.
It's also the home of the headquarters of
the organization set up to help adventurers,
the Free Union, which Fuze
and his people belong to.
That's because its location is
easily accessible from all nations.
The school where these kids are,
Freedom Academy, was established
by one of Shizu-san's students.
That student's name is Yuuki Kagurazaka.
Based on the name, they must be Japanese...
My plan is to meet them first.
Fuze wrote a letter of introduction
for me, so that won't be a problem.
Kingdom of Ingrassia
Thanks to Ranga,
I arrived at the royal capital of
Ingrassia in just three days.
Stay hidden in my shadow.
It'll cause a panic if you
walk into the city like this.
Yes, Master. Feel free to
call upon me at any time.
Take care.
Sure.
There was a strict identification
policy for entering the capital.
Just in case there was a magic barrier
to prevent monsters from entering,
I wore the magic-suppressing
mask to conceal my aura.
It'd probably be trouble if
they found out I'm a monster,
so it's just in case.
And, with the ID that Fuze prepared for me,
I was able to enter the
capital without issue.
Sorry...
There are so many people.
It's quite a departure
from our little nation.
Definitely a big city.
Whoa, seriously?!
Is that glass?
This is the biggest pane of glass
I've seen since I came to this world.
This must be a church.
Wait... Don't churches
consider monsters enemies?
Better make sure I don't
get involved with that.
Free Union Headquarters
And that must be the Free Union headquarters.
Glass here, too...
They definitely have money.
Automatic doors?!
I've verified your letter of introduction.
The Grandmaster has agreed
to see you. I'll show you in.
Right this way.
Thanks.
We're teleporting? They must be
worried about spies and stuff.
Please wait here for a few moments.
Now... What will this Grandmaster be like?
Thank you for waiting.
Pleased to meet you.
Grandmaster  Yuuki Kagurazaka
I'm the Grandmaster, Yuuki Kaguraza... ka...
Nice to meet you, too. I'm Rimuru Tempest.
I'm the leader of the
Jura Tempest Federation,
the nation of monsters in the Forest of Jura.
That mask... is Shizu-sensei's.
That's right. You know who I am, don't you?
I'm a slime that can mimic the
appearance of monsters I eat.
Monsters you... eat?
Calm down, kid.
I'm not a bad slime.
That line...
I beat that game, too.
You taught it to Shizu-san, didn't you?
I'd like you to elaborate further on this.
That's why I'm here.
I see! So that's what happens
in the last episode!
Wow, so Belldandy really...
Anything else you'd like to know?
By the time I got stabbed and died,
I'd finished just about all
the manga and anime you know!
Naturally, I didn't miss
a thing in that respect.
It's important to get the basics down.
That's how a gentleman's gotta be.
You amaze me, Master Rimuru!
Please, please teach me!
What about games?
How many FFs were they up to?
Nineteen.
That many?!
Anything else?
The Sagrada Família is almost finished.
Wow! Finally?!
And Iitomo ended.
Are you serious?!
What am I gonna be "Uki Uki Watching"
every weekday afternoon now?!
BomBom is gone.
What?! I looked forward to those
comics every month as a kid!
Hey! Is that one series
finished yet? Glass Ma—
Nope, it's still going.
Still?! Then... Then what
about The Five Sta—
Well, since each book has
its own clear ending...
So it still hasn't ended?
I'd love to know how it's
going to end myself.
As for the prime ministers we've had...
Oh, I don't care about that.
Huh?!
Still, that's incredible. I'm so happy.
Just hearing all this has been great,
but I wish I could've seen
it all with my own eyes.
Your own eyes, huh?
Got any paper?
Paper?
Hang on a sec.
Transform!
Oh! So this is your true form!
Sirius
Here's a whole volume.
Wow! What magic did you
use to make this, Master?!
That's a trade secret.
It was the result of using
Great Sage's ability to the fullest.
I copied images from my own memory
onto the paper I ingested.
Notice. This is a waste of my ability.
Waste
You fool! This is an extremely
effective use of your ability!
Well, you'd better get me more paper,
if you want to read what comes next.
Thank you so much, Master!
Now, do you see that I'm not a bad slime?
Of course!
The news about Shizu-sensei is unfortunate,
but I trust you.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
I'll take my time reading these later.
Land of the Lustrous
So, what brought you here to see me?
Are you looking for a way
to go back home, perhaps?
No, it's not that...
but is it possible to go back?
Well, if it was, I'm sure you
would've done it long ago.
I've given up on that. I've probably
been cremated by now, anyway.
It sounds like you have no way back.
But I don't believe that it's impossible.
There were legends of
ogres and demons in Japan,
and every other nation has
similar myths and stories, too.
So I figure that if some condition is met,
moving between our worlds should be possible.
I see...
If your goal wasn't to go back,
then why are you here?
I'm more than happy to
just live an easy life.
I built a town, and I intended to
enjoy life with my friends there.
But there was something bothering me.
What was bothering you?
Shizu-sensei's lingering regret.
I see. Shizu-sensei's regret...
The children of Freedom Academy.
If that is Shizu-sensei's wish, then...
Of course.
Rimuru-san, I'm also willing
to entrust them to you.
Yuuki arranged for me to
be a teacher at the school.
I'll be the one teaching
Shizu-sensei's students now.
Incidentally, it comes with
a dorm just for the teachers!
Three meals a day, too!
My daily wage is ten silver coins.
The working conditions are pretty good!
Rimuru-san, do you know Hinata Sakaguchi?
Hinata Sakaguchi?
She was once a student of Shizu-sensei's.
Oh...
The one who left Shizu-san?
Yes.
In her prime, Shizu-sensei had complete
control over the superior spirit Ifrit,
but Hinata gained strength surpassing
hers at the age of fifteen.
Huh...
That alone should give you
an idea of how strong she is.
Nope, not a clue.
Better just keep my mouth shut.
You may wonder why I'm
telling you about this...
I just want you to know the difference
between the Otherworlders,
like Hinata and us,
who came to this world spontaneously,
and those five students, the Summons.
Summons?
Veldora mentioned that...
A Summon?
Is that different from Otherworlders?
It takes more than 30 mages to perform
a ritual that lasts several days
to bring one here from another world.
They're also expected to
serve as powerful weapons.
Weapons?
Yes, for the Summoner.
Magic is used to carve a
curse into the Summon's soul
to ensure that the Summon
can't defy the Summoner.
Since Summons are brought here
for some specific purpose,
they're always given power
suited to that purpose.
Just like the Hero who may become
mankind's trump card, in fact.
When crossing worlds,
one is given a new body.
At that time, the body takes
in a massive amount of energy
and begins to acquire abilities.
When a summoning is performed,
there are times when a child is summoned.
And when an amount of energy too vast
for that child's growing body is taken in...
Eventually, that body will be incinerated
by all that energy with nowhere to go.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
So those five kids you mentioned...
You surmised correctly. They were summoned.
Are they okay, then?
They resulted when different nations
tried and failed to summon a Hero.
Shizu-sensei took them in and
did her best to save them.
Different nations? Whole nations
are involved in summoning?
Yes. I suppose that was this world's choice.
Rather than strengthening armies
so they can face monsters,
it may be more effective to summon an
Otherworlder of incomparable strength.
That's what they thought.
If you know Shizu-sensei's strength,
I'm sure you understand what that implies.
But...
Shizu-san hated this world.
So what's going to happen to these kids?
The longest any Summon has lasted
according to our current records...
is five years.
Five years?
No one has found a way to
prevent their destruction.
Nearly all children under the age
of ten who have been summoned
have died within five years.
The nations willingly let us have these
children because of that, but still...
So no matter what I do with these kids,
the nations won't complain, right?
You have something in mind?
Yeah.
If that's Shizu-san's wish, I'll take it on.
Please!
If it's at all possible,
please save those children!
I'll just do whatever I can.
It's what I've always done,
and what I'll continue to do.
Right!
Heya! Starting today, I'm your new te—
Wait... I thought these
kids didn't have long left?
Aren't they just giving all that
excess energy free rein to run wild?
Ken-chan, you're awesome!
Is that your finishing move?
You finally perfected it!
It wasn't good enough, though. He dodged it.
Shut up! I won't miss next time!
No way! No way! This is no good at all!
This classroom is pure chaos!
He looks... a little like Shizu-sensei.
Huh? You think so?
He doesn't look a bit like her.
Kenya Misaki
Kenya Misaki, age 10.
Ryota Sekiguchi
Ryota Sekiguchi, age 10.
Gale Gibson, age 11.
Gale Gibson
Alice Rondo, age 9.
Alice Rondo
Chloe Aubert
Chloe Aubert, age 10.
I just felt something react...
Was that Veldora?
Anyway, since they're not
supposed to have much time left,
I expected these kids to be meek and mild...
That's a bit depressing.
Next time, "Shizu-san's Students."
Shizu-san's  Students