The Storm Dragon Veldora was
sealed by Unlimited Imprisonment.
Unlimited Imprisonment
To break that seal, Rimuru ate Veldora.
They both began the process
of analyzing the seal,
Veldora from the inside and
Rimuru from the outside,
with the goal of setting
Veldora free someday.
After gaining several new
skills and leaving the cave,
Rimuru met the Goblins,
and he ended up vowing to protect
them from an attack by Direwolves.
That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
Episode 3: Battle at the Goblin Village
Looks like I shouldn't expect to
find many who can fight Direwolves.
They all look too scrawny and beat-up.
Talk about pressure...
Everyone, do you understand our situation?
Yes!
We are prepared for a life-or-death battle!
No need to get all worked up. Just relax.
Think only about doing the best you can.
I didn't mean to sound that cool...
But first, take me to where the wounded are.
We did all we could for them, but...
That's deeper than I'd imagined.
Did their claws and fangs
do that much damage?
Well, might as well try it...
Wh-What are you doing?!
Huh? I'm...
Y-Your wounds...
They're healed!
I guess it never hurts to try!
I never thought eating him and throwing
all those potions in my body at him
would be so effective!
These healing potions really work!
Next! And next!
Since I ate all those hipokute
herbs, I've got plenty to spare!
I'll heal 'em all!
Y-You are magnificent, Rimuru-sama!
That's the last of the wounded.
Now, then...
We'll build a fence.
Fortify the village's defenses!
Right.
Great Forest of Jura
It's a fine night.
Veldora's protection has
vanished from this forest.
We have nothing to fear any longer.
Tonight, we will destroy the Goblin Village
and create a foothold here
in the Great Forest of Jura!
We will rule this forest!
Our claws can tear apart any monster,
and our fangs can chew any monster to pieces!
Hah!
What good will such a flimsy fence do?
Father...
A slime?
Turn back now, and we won't take any action.
Leave this place at once!
Insolence! No mere slime can
order around us Direwolves!
Trample down that fence!
Spill the blood of those lowly Goblins!
Threads?
That's my skill, Steel Thread.
— Steel Thread —
This is your doing?
That's right!
A puny monster like you dares do this?!
I will squash you!
Father!
Rimuru-sama!
That's Sticky Thread.
— Sticky Thread —
This won't hold me!
Skill: Water Blade!
Hear me, Direwolves!
Your boss is dead!
I'll give you the choice: submit or die!
Yikes...
What if they go the "We'd rather die than
submit" route and attack all at once?
I wish they'd just turn tail and run...
Oh! Predator!
Analysis complete.
Acquired ability to mimic Direwolf.
Acquired ability to mimic Direwolf
Direwolf species skills Supreme Sense of Smell,
Thought Communication, and Menace acquired.
Thought
Communication
Supreme Sense
of Smell
Direwolf Species Skills
Menace
Right!
— Mimic —
Hear me! I will let you go just this once.
If you refuse to yield to me,
I will allow you to leave this place!
— Menace —
Come on, run away already!
It's not working? They still want to fight?
Our pack yields to you.
Huh?
They could have just run away...
U-Um...
D-Did we win?
Yeah, looks that way.
It's good that there's no
need for fighting anymore.
Yep, yep. Nothing beats peace.
And so the battle at the Goblin
Village ended remarkably easily.
But...
What now?
Who's gonna look after not only the
Goblins, but all these pups, too?
I guess their numbers are
about the same. Then...
Okay, listen up!
So, I'm going to have you all
pair up and live together!
Pair... up?
Do you understand?
Rimuru-sama, what does "pair" mean, exactly?
It means to form groups of two.
Groups...
...of two?
Good!
Yesterday's enemy is today's friend!
You're all to work together and get
along as friends from now on! Got it?
Yes, sir!
Help each other out, and make it work.
That settles things for now...
So, um...
What's going to be important now
is food, shelter, and clothing.
We should form teams to hunt
for food, build houses,
and strengthen the village defenses.
We'll start with...
What was his name again?
Wait, do they even have names?
Hey, what are all of your names, anyway?
We monsters do not normally have names.
Even without names, we can still
communicate our thoughts to one another.
Oh, really?
But it's more convenient to have names,
so I'd like to name you all. Is that okay?
N-Name us?
A-Are you certain?
S-Sure.
Why are they so excited over something
as simple as getting a name?
Okay, we'll start with you.
Hmm, let's see...
What did you call the son
you had who died in battle?
Rigur.
Rigur, huh?
Then you'll be Rigurd.
Rigurd!
Thank you so much! Rigurd! I am so moved!
R-Really?
I just picked it because
it had the same sound...
You'll inherit your brother's name: Rigur.
Yes, sir!
I'm so grateful that my son has been
allowed to inherit Rigur's name!
Thank you so much!
Where the heck are these
reactions coming from?
You're Gobta.
Y-Yes, sir! Thank you, sir!
You're Gobchi.
Gobtsu.
Gobte.
And you're Gobzo.
These names are getting
more and more careless...
I feel bad seeing them so happy.
Um... We truly do appreciate
you giving us all names, but...
We are aware that your
magical power is immense,
but are you sure it's all right
to give all of us names at once?
Well, I don't see any problem.
Well, if you are certain...
Who's next?
You'll be... Haruna!
Okay!
That takes care of all the Goblins.
Next is...
He's the son of the Direwolf boss, isn't he?
I wonder if he holds a grudge against me...
Actually...
They don't seem to be
holding any grudges at all.
Hmm...
Wolf, fangs...
Wind... Storm...
I know. I'll give him my family name.
Tempest...
Tempest Fang...
Storm Fang...
Ranga...
Oh! Ranga! I like that!
All right! Your name is Ranga!
— (Storm)   (Fang) —
Ranga...
I think he likes it.
Wh-What's going on? My body...
Rimuru-sama?!
Everything... is getting... dark...
Rimuru-sama!
Please stay strong!
Warning.
Warning
Magicule reserves below minimum limit
Internal magicule reserves have
fallen below the minimum limit.
Entering sleep mode.
Estimated time to full recovery: three days.
I used up too many magicules?
How...?
I couldn't move, speak,
or sense my surroundings,
but I was conscious.
It must have been because he
named so many of us at once...
Apparently, giving names to
monsters uses up magicules.
I guess that's why Rigurd was so worried.
Is that common knowledge among monsters?
You should've said so!
Then, three days later...
Full recovery!
Oh, Rimuru-sama!
Good morning!
Y-Yeah...
You seem to be all better.
Who's this?
I'll go get Elder Rigurd.
Uh, okay.
Did this village have a girl that cute in it?
Rimuru-sama! Have you awakened?!
Oh, Rigurd!
That woman who... was... just...
Who are you?!
I am Rigurd.
What happened in the last three days?!
It's because you gave us names!
Just from that?!
Becoming a monster with a name
raises one's rank as a monster
and causes one to evolve!
I-I see...
So that's why you were all so
happy just to be getting names.
No wonder that sucked my magicules dry...
Master, allow me to express my
utmost joy at your recovery!
That horn... The star on your forehead...
You're Ranga, right?
Yes!
Rimuru-sama!
There's Rigurd...
And Rigur...
And Gobta...
Well, you didn't change much.
Rimuru-sama! Rimuru-sama!
It's not so much like they evolved.
They're like totally different monsters.
The male Goblins have evolved to Hobgoblins,
and the females to Goblinas.
Ranga, if I recall, you were
the only Direwolf I named...
so why did all of the Direwolves evolve?
Master, all of us Direwolves are as one.
Our brethren are all connected.
Therefore, my name has
become our clan's name.
Huh... So your entire clan
evolved through a shared name?
We are no longer the Direwolves.
We are the Tempest Wolves!
Tempest Wolves...
Well, good for you!
Master!
Can't you show a little consideration?!
I-I'm so sorry!
You can change your own size?! That's handy!
Well, the evolving isn't so bad.
The problem is what to
do about food, shelter,
and clothing to sustain both
the Goblins and the Wolves...
Master!
Right, it took five minutes
for all of you to quiet down.
They didn't get my best joke?!
Rimuru-sama, what did you mean by that?
F-Forget about it.
As you can see, we're a huge family now.
So to avoid problems, I think
we should set some rules.
Rules?
There are three rules.
I'd like you to uphold
them, at the very least.
First, no attacking humans.
Second, no fighting amongst yourselves.
Third, no belittling other races.
That's it.
Sir!
Yes, Rigur-kun!
Why aren't we allowed to attack humans?
H-Hey! Rigur!
It's all right.
The reason is simple.
It's because I like humans. That's it!
I see! Now I understand!
Huh? You... understand?
Really?
Um, so, listen... Humans live in groups.
If you mess with them,
they could retaliate in a big way.
And if they came after us in earnest,
I doubt we could handle them.
Besides, getting along benefits
us in lots of ways, anyway.
Any other questions?
Me!
Gobta-kun!
What did you mean by
"no belittling other races"?
Well, you've all gotten
stronger by evolving, right?
It means you shouldn't let that get to
your head and push weaker races around.
Don't make the mistake of thinking
you're better than them.
You don't want them getting stronger
themselves and retaliating someday, do you?
Got it, sir!
That's about it. Do your
best to follow those rules.
Yes, sir!
Also...
Elder Rigurd, I declare you the Goblin Lord.
The lord of the Goblins!
Lord?!
Lead your village well.
Yes, sir!
I, Rigurd, accept this
responsibility on pain of death!
Good. I'm counting on you.
Frankly, I was just dumping the job on
him. I didn't expect him to be so moved.
I then gave jobs to all the Goblins.
I assigned a team to keep watch
on the surrounding area...
and a team to gather food.
It doesn't look like there'll
be any problems with these two.
The problem is...
The team that builds houses, and
the team that makes clothes.
The "shelter and clothing" part
of "food, shelter, and clothing."
I wouldn't call that a house.
I can't do any more than
basic handyman stuff,
but I worked in general contracting,
so I know good from bad.
And this...
You don't need to be a general
contractor to figure it out.
This is most embarrassing.
Forgive us.
And as for your clothes...
I-I think they're a little too revealing!
That's not necessarily a bad thing, but...
There is no one here with
the skill to make them.
Huh?
I-If you can't make them,
couldn't you get some from somewhere?
There are some with whom we have
attempted to trade a few times.
Aside from clothing,
they are also quite skilled,
so they may know how to build houses, too.
Hmm...
Well, we're getting nowhere this way,
so maybe we should go see them.
Who, and where, are they?
They are the Dwarves,
and they live in Dwargon.
Dwarves!
You mean the famous
masters of metalworking?!
Now I have no choice but to go!
I'll try going to Dwargon.
Rigurd, can you look after
the village while I'm away?
Yes, sir!
Leave everything to me!
All right, I'll see you later!
Goodbye!
Safe travels!
Come back soon!
And so I left the village
to go and meet the Dwarves.
I'm told this Dwargon place
is a pretty big city,
and it even has a king.
I'm a little... no, I'm really excited!
Next time, "In the Kingdom of the Dwarves."
In the Kingdom of the Dwarves