Mommy! What about the bomb shelter?
Mommy!
Tokyo: Present Day
Sure is peaceful...
I live a totally normal, uneventful life.
I graduated from college, got a job
at a major general contracting firm,
worked my way up the ladder,
and started making decent money.
I'm a perfectly content 37-year-old man.
If there's anything missing in my
life right now, it's a girlfriend.
In fact, I haven't had a
girlfriend in all my 37 years...
But not having one doesn't
bother me at all, really.
Senpai!
Over here, Senpai!
Tamura, sorry I'm a bit late.
So, what'd you want to discuss?
Hello! I'm Sawatari Miho.
I see you around a lot, but this
is our first time speaking.
Oh... Hi. I'm Mikami Satoru.
I know who you are, of course. You're famous.
What?! Famous?!
Yeah, I mean, all those rumors...
Wh-What rumors?!
Easy, Miho. He's just teasing you.
Go easy on her, Senpai.
Sorry about that.
What is this, anyway?
Is he looking for marriage advice?
No need to stand around.
Let's talk while we eat.
You like yakiniku, don't you, Senpai?
I booked a great place for us.
Jeez, he arranged one of
my favorites for dinner?
Kid sure knows how to treat his senpai.
It's just up ahead.
Well, I guess I should offer
them my congratulations.
Tamura!
S-Senpai!
Wh-What is this?
It's too hot...
I don't... want this...
Confirmed.
Heat Resistance acquisition successful.
How the hell could I get stabbed and die?!
It hurts
Confirmed.
Get Stabbed and Die
Stab Resistance acquisition successful.
Stab Resistance
Continuing...
Continuing
Physical Attack Resistance
acquisition successful.
Acquisition
Successful.
We need an ambulance! Quick!
It hurts... The blood...
Confirmed.
Pain Nullification
Pain Nullification acquired.
[Acquired]
Pain
Nullification
Creating a body that does not require blood.
Creating a body that
does not require blood
Successful.
Would you... shut up already, Tamura?
Senpai, hang in there!
So cold...
Cold Resistance acquisition successful.
Heat Resistance
Cold Resistance
Acquisition of Heat Resistance
and Cold Resistance
Thermal Fluctuation Resistance
results in acquisition of new skill,
Thermal Fluctuation Resistance.
Am I... gonna die?
T-Tamura...
Take the hard drive out
of my computer at home...
put it in the bath... and make
sure it's completely wiped.
Huh?
Deletion of data via electric current
has failed due to insufficient information.
Consistency not found among theoretical values.
As an alternate measure,
Employing Alternate Measure
Electric Current Resistance acquired.
Electric Current Resistance
Attached is Paralysis Resistance.
Paralysis Resistance
Acquisition successful.
Successful.
Senpai...
Please...
All I really wanted to do...
was show off Sawatari to you...
Jeez...
Don't worry about that.
Mikami-san...
Be sure to make her happy.
And take care of my computer.
I never thought I'd die a virgin...
If I'm reborn, I'll be a lot more aggressive.
I'll screw every girl I see...
Unique skill: Predator
acquisition successful.
Unique Skill
Predator
Acquired
If a guy who's still a
virgin at 30 is a magician,
then, given how close I was
to 40, I would've been a sage.
I could've even made it
to the rank of great sage.
Extra skill: Sage acquisition successful.
Extra Skill
Sage
Acquired
Continuing, Sage will transform
into the unique skill Great Sage.
Sage will transform into
the unique skill Great Sage
Unique Skill
Great Sage
Successful.
Unique Skill
Great Sage
Successful
Oh, shut up...
Just let me... have some... quiet time...
Senpai...
Senpai!
I can't see anything.
Episode 1: The Storm Dragon, Verudora
Where am I?
And... what happened?
I feel like someone was teasing me
about being a sage, or a great sage...
That's right... I was stabbed and...
Okay, I remember. It's all right.
This isn't the time to panic yet.
The only time I ever lost my cool was
when I crapped my pants in grade school.
Okay, so... I was stabbed, and then...
I don't... hurt anywhere.
I'm not cold.
My eyes... won't open?
I can't see anything!
My hands... my feet...
I can't feel them.
My body...
I can move!
So I have sensation.
Are those... rocks?
Rock
Which would mean I'm not in the hospital...
Then, where the hell am I?
Is this...
some kind of plant?
Does my mouth work?
My voice...
Nope.
Huh? It dissolved?
Plant
Intake
It's permeating throughout my body...
Disappear
Surge
What's happened to me?
Something seems weird.
Humans can't usually
dissolve plants, can they?
Oh... Huh? Eh?
Maybe I really did die...
What happened to Tamura and Sawatari-san?
Did he wipe my hard drive?
Just... what the heck am I right now?
Hey, I bounce. I seem
to have some elasticity.
Let's see, my body's exterior is...
Uh-huh.
I see, I see.
How can this be?!
I was such a hot,
manly man (self-proclaimed),
Manly
(Self-proclaimed)
but now I've taken on this
refined, streamlined form!
Yeah, right, idiot!
Like hell I can accept that!
But... I am a slime, aren't I?
Yeah. I'm not human.
It seems like I got stabbed,
died, and reincarnated...
as a slime.
I think it's been a fairly
long time since then.
Surprisingly, it turns out
this body is pretty handy.
I don't even need to eat or sleep.
So why do I eat plants, you ask?
Because I have nothing else to do!
There's no point, but I don't feel
right if I'm not doing something.
Wait... Who am I even talking to?
Anyway, I wonder where
this stuff I eat is going.
I haven't pooped or...
Answer.
It is stored in the stomach
of your unique skill, Predator.
Th-That voice... I heard
it when I was stabbed, too!
Wh-Who are you?
Answer.
It is the effect of your
unique skill, Great Sage.
Unique Skill
Great Sage
In Effect
Now that your ability is established,
Ability
Established
you are capable of reacting more quickly.
Reaction Speed
Up
Great Sage...
So, um, does "skill" mean my abilities?
What is "Predator"?
It allows you to ingest objects
and analyze them within your body.
Unique Skill
Predator
Mimicry Skill
You can then acquire that object's skills.
Absorb Into Body
Analyze
Parallel
Once the analysis is complete, you
can mimic the object, as well.
Oh!
The stomach stores the objects you ingest.
It can also isolate harmful
objects that cannot be analyzed.
Th-This "Predator" seems like
a pretty amazing ability.
Is it really something a slime should have?
But, hey, since I do have it...
As a test, can you analyze the plants I ate?
Analysis complete.
Hipokute herbs.
Hipokute Herbs
A valuable herb that only grows
in areas rich in magicules.
in areas rich in magicules,
used in healing potions.
Used as an ingredient in
salves and healing potions.
Magicules?
Magicules
Magicules.
A special energetic material found in all—
A special energetic material found in all...
Explain it so I can understand!
Magical Beings
Magicules
They are the building blocks
of life in all magical beings.
Building blocks of life?
I get it. This cave must
be full of that stuff,
which is why all these valuable
herbs grow here, right?
So I can analyze these hipokute herbs
and store them in my stomach.
Does that mean I can create and
store salves and healing potions
within my own body?
Affirmative
Precisely.
I see!
Okay, then...
So I gobbled up all the
hipokute herbs in this cave
and immediately turned them into
potions in my stomach along the way.
Potion
They could come in handy
if I'm ever in trouble...
but mostly, I just have nothing else to do.
If all those plants are actually some
valuable herb you call hipokute herbs,
does that mean this rock
is worth something, too?
Magistone ore.
Magistone
Ore
Minerals that spend long periods
of time in magicule-rich areas
take in magicules until
they become magistone ore.
It is very valuable.
Really?! Okay, then!
Magistone ore's pretty awesome, too!
So I gobbled up all the
magistone ore in the cave.
And there's a ton of it!
It's an all-you-can-eat buffet!
Um... Did I just... fall in water?
A lake?
So slimes don't float?
Am I really gonna die this time?
I don't feel like I'm suffocating.
Wait, was I even breathing to begin with?
I guess I wasn't...
But what do I do now?
This looks bad.
I know!
I'll just ingest some water and...
Okay!
Skill: Water Pressure Propulsion acquired.
— Water Pressure Propulsion —
W-Wait... I'm going a little too fast!
I'm pretty sure I hit that wall,
but I don't feel any pain.
Answer.
Pain Nullification
Because you have acquired Pain Nullification,
you will not feel pain.
The physical damage you have taken is 10%.
Notice
Physical Damage Taken
10%
Species skill Self-Regeneration
has been activated.
Species Skill
Self-Regeneration
Activated
So I still take damage,
even though I don't feel pain?
I repaired the part of me that took damage?
This body really is convenient!
But I guess I should be more careful.
Can you hear me, small one?
Hey! I know you can hear me!
Y-You're talking to me, aren't you?
Answer me.
Easy for you to say!
How am I supposed to talk
when I don't have a mouth?!
Hey!
Just shut up already, baldy!
Oh? You called me a baldy, eh?
I see you have guts.
Uh...
I was trying to be nice since I
haven't had a visitor in so long,
but you seem to have a death wish.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I had no idea you could hear my thoughts!
I don't have a mouth or even eyes, you see...
It amazed me that you would say
such a thing after seeing me,
but it turns out you can't see me, eh?
All right. I will give you sight.
Huh?
However, there will be conditions.
What do you say?
What sort of conditions?
It's simple.
You must not fear me when you
have the ability to see me,
and you must come talk to me again.
That's all.
A good deal for you, is it not?
That's all I have to do?
Yes. You see, I was sealed
here 300 years ago.
Ever since then, I've had nothing
to do, and it's unbearably boring.
What do you say?
I'm curious as to why you were sealed, but...
Okay, I'll gladly do it!
Very well. There is a
skill called Magic Sense.
Can you use it?
No, I can't.
It allows you to sense
the magicules around you.
If I can detect magicules,
I'll be able to see?
Okay, I guess I'll try it.
Hey, there's something...
Is this the stuff you call magicules?
Extra skill: Magic Sense acquired.
Extra Skill
Magic Sense
Acquired
That easily?!
Also, "extra"?
Extra?
Skills with power and efficiency magnitudes
higher than those of normal skills.
Magic Sense
Wow! "Extra" sounds awesome!
Would you like to use Magic Sense?
Yes!
I can see!
I can actually see!
Oh, yeah!
I really am a slime.
Well?
Oh, right!
I did it!
Thanks so much!
D-Dragon?!
Allow me to formally introduce myself.
O-Okay...
I am the Storm Dragon, Verudora.
Storm Dragon?
I am one of only four True Dragons
that exist in this world.
Hey, you do remember our promise, don't you?
O-Of course! I'm not scared at all!
Well, I'll come to chat again sometime!
Hold it!
This is indeed unusual.
Slimes are normally low-ranked
monsters that don't think,
but you have self-awareness.
Are you Unique?
What does "Unique" mean?
It refers to a being with
extraordinary abilities.
I'm not really sure.
The thing is, I used to be a human,
but I got stabbed and died, and next
thing I knew, I looked like this.
I see. You were reincarnated.
Reincarnated...
So I really was reborn as a slime...
You came into this world
in a very unusual way.
Huh? Unusual?
There are occasionally those who
come here from other worlds,
but you are the first I've known
of to be reincarnated here.
Most would be unable to withstand having
only their soul traverse worlds.
So you're saying
there are people who came here from other
worlds, but not through reincarnation?
Indeed. We call them Otherworlders.
I've heard that they gain special abilities
when they cross into this world.
I see... I guess that's
how I got my skills, too.
There might even be other
Japanese people here...
I think I'd like to try and find
some of these Otherworlders.
What? You're leaving already?
He's pouting!
U-Um... Maybe I'll stay a little longer.
It's not like I have anything to do...
Oh, good! Stay as long as you like!
So, um, you said earlier that
you were sealed here, right?
I'm glad you asked that!
It was 300 years ago...
I sort of turned a town into ashes by mistake.
"Sort of"?
So someone came looking to slay me.
It's certainly true that I
underestimated my opponent a bit.
I started putting my full strength
into the battle partway through...
But I still lost!
But you seem really strong.
Was your opponent that powerful?
Yes, very powerful.
It was someone known to the humans as
a hero blessed with divine protection.
A human hero? Sounds like
something out of a video game.
She overpowered me with her unique
skill, Absolute Severance,
— Absolute Severance —
and then she sealed me using
Unlimited Imprisonment.
Unlimited Imprisonment
Is that shiny stuff her
Unlimited Imprisonment?
Yes.
The hero called herself a "Summon."
Summon
A Summon?
Is that different from Otherworlders?
It takes more than 30 mages to perform
a ritual that lasts several days
to bring one here from another world.
Oh! So there are mages here!
This sounds more and more like a game!
They're also expected to
serve as powerful weapons.
Weapons?
Yes, for the Summoner.
Magic is used to carve a
curse into the Summon's soul
to ensure that the Summon
can't defy the Summoner.
What the heck?! That's just cruel!
Cruel, eh?
I don't know what your world was like,
but survival of the fittest is the
prevailing truth in this world.
I see...
So you've been in here ever
since that hero sealed you?
That's right.
I'm so very bored...
I felt pretty damn lonely just because
I never had a girlfriend in 37 years...
I can't imagine being all alone for 300 years.
Okay!
Why don't you and I be friends?
What?! A mere slime proposes friendship
with me, the feared Storm Dragon?!
I-If you don't want to, I understand...
F-Fool! No one said I didn't want to!
Uh, really? Then... what do you say?
Yes, well... if you insist...
I guess I'm willing to think about it.
Are you some tsundere?!
Yes, I insist! So that settles it!
If you refuse, we're through.
I'll never come here again!
W-Well, all right. I'll be your friend.
You'd better be grateful!
Just can't be honest, can you?
Well, glad to know ya!
I-Indeed.
It's a little embarrassing talking
about "friends" at my age...
But that's the story of
how I got stabbed, died,
reincarnated as a slime,
and became friends with
the Storm Dragon Verudora.
My totally normal,
uneventful life... is no more.
How could this have happened?
I never dreamed a life like
this was waiting for me!
Or should I call it a "slife"?
I wonder if Tamura wiped
my hard drive for me...
I hope he didn't look at it first.
* Never attempt this.
Rest in peace, Senpai.
If I ever have a son, I'll name him Satoru.
Next time, "Meeting the Goblins."
Meeting the Goblins