That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
The Ameld River
Free Union  Blumund Guild
Episode 6: Shizu
There's no sign that the Eastern Empire is
trying to cross the Great Forest of Jura.
Not yet, at least.
Our intelligence bureau is
continuing to monitor them.
Guildmaster Fuze
So, how did it go in the
Great Forest of Jura?
It was a disaster!
Can't you even say you're glad
we came back in one piece?
Let's hear your report.
Seriously? We just got back.
Kaval  Job Class: Fighter
Eren  Job Class: Sorcerer
I really want a bath...
Gido  Job Class: Thief
You think you two had it rough?
I had to listen to you
squabbling the whole time.
Um...
While in the cave, we confirmed
Veldora's disappearance.
We then searched the cave,
but we found nothing.
Nothing?
No, nothing.
I'm now clear on what happened in the cave.
Then we'll just be—
I'll give you three days off.
Huh?
Next, instead of the cave, you'll
investigate around the forest.
The monsters may be more
active with Veldora gone.
Don't overlook any changes,
no matter how small.
Be thorough. Search every nook and cranny.
You may go.
"You may go," my ass!
Why only three days?!
Give us a longer break!
We just got back, you know!
I wish you would've said all
this to the guildmaster.
That stupid old geezer!
Give us a longer break!
We have to go back to that forest?
Jeez, can't we do anything but complain?
It's making me feel worse.
I want my bath...
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Did you not say you are going
to the Great Forest of Jura?
What if we did?
Would you allow me to accompany
you through the forest?
Sure!
Hey!
I'm the leader! You can't
give the okay before I do!
Why not?
Traveling is best with companions,
and life is best with compassion.
Eren, Kaval, and Gido.
Shizu.
Welcome aboard, Shizu!
Sheesh...
We leave in three days.
If that's okay with you,
come along if you want.
I appreciate it.
Ready, Ranga. Watch closely.
I shall!
Rimuru, transform!
— Tempest Star Wolf —
And now... Black Lightning!
Black Lightning
Wow.
I thought I'd try out the
new skill I just learned,
but I'll have to be careful how I
use it. It could be too powerful.
Black Lightning...
You never cease to amaze, Master!
Ah... Everything's so peaceful.
Uh-huh. Looks like they're doing great.
A few weeks had passed since Rimuru
returned from Dwargon with Kaijin
and the other dwarves.
Kaijin
Strike while the iron's hot, as we say!
There's the blacksmith, Kaijin,
with expert smithing skills...
The oldest of the three dwarf
brothers, Garm, an armor smith...
Garm
Tanning hides makes them more durable.
Dord
The middle brother, Dord, whose
craftsmanship is the finest among all dwarves...
And the youngest brother, Myrd,
Myrd
whose skill with his hands makes him
an expert in architecture and the arts.
With their guidance,
Rimuru and the Goblins were well on
their way to building a new village.
When we first came back from Dwargon,
I was a little surprised to
see what had happened...
Uh, Rigurd... What is this?
They all heard the rumors about you
and came here from the nearby Goblin
villages to seek protection.
O-Oh...
Welcome home, Rimuru-sama!
Great Sage, how many of them are there?
Answer: approximately 500.
Fi—
I thought about asking them to leave, but...
What will happen if I turn them away?
Due to the disappearance of
the Storm Dragon, Veldora,
Orcs, Lizardmen, Ogres,
and other intelligent monster races are vying
for dominance in the Great Forest of Jura.
The unevolved Goblins will
likely be eliminated.
You answered that so easily...
All right. Come with us, all who want to.
So Rimuru named all 500 of the Goblins...
and spent three days asleep again.
I wasn't sure how it'd work out,
but it's starting to look like
they'll all be able to live here.
Good job, Kaijin!
All right! I'll show you how it's done!
Whoa! He summoned one!
There you have it.
Give it a try, all of you!
Gobta is teaching the newbies
how to summon a Tempest Wolf.
Never knew Gobta had it in him...
When Rimuru nearly left Gobta
behind in the Dwarven Kingdom...
He prayed with all his might for help.
And when he did...
he succeeded in summoning his wolf.
He then rode the wolf out of the kingdom,
rejoined Rimuru's party, and made
it back to the village safely.
I guess that boy can do
things when he really tries.
Rimuru's opinion of Gobta went
up several levels after that.
That won't work.
You've gotta be more like, "Unnnngh"...
And then, "Pop!" Like that!
He's not the greatest teacher, though.
Rimuru's opinion of Gobta went
down several levels after that.
Rimuru-sama!
Rigurd.
By the way, Rigurd was promoted
from Goblin Lord to Goblin King.
He's the leader of all the other
village elders who joined us.
Frankly, they threw the job at him.
It seems like becoming the Goblin
King made him evolve even further...
Is something up?
Yes, sir! We received a message
from Rigur and the security team.
It seems they've discovered
suspicious beings in the forest.
Monsters?
No, humans.
Humans?
They may be scouts from some nation
hoping to expand its dominion.
Hmm...
This is your fault, Kaval!
You just had to stab a
Giant Ant nest with your sword!
Shut up! Don't complain about your leader!
For a leader, you're way too careless!
If I die, I swear I'll
come back to haunt you!
That's not even possible!
Because...
I'd be dying with you!
Shizu!
No, don't!
W-Wow...
Shizu, that one's still—
Shizu!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes.
What the heck was that?
It looked like... black lightning.
I guess Black Lightning really is too strong.
Better not use it, either.
A slime?
Yeah. Got a problem with slimes?
Uh, no...
I just never knew slimes could talk.
I can't believe it.
Here, miss. This is yours, isn't it?
Sorry about that.
You weren't hurt, were you?
No, I'm all right.
I met her sooner than I expected...
You saved me. Thank you.
The one I'm destined to be with.
What are those four up to?
Well...
Hey, damn it! I wanted that meat!
What a jerk! I raised that
meat myself, you know!
Listen, man! I won't yield
when it comes to food!
I'm sorry...
They said they were starving,
so I gave them food.
Hey, that's great!
Helping those in need is a good thing!
Yes, sir! Thank you very much!
I hope to dedicate myself to doing just that!
Good, good.
Rimuru-sama, go on in.
Now that I really look at them,
I feel like I've seen them before...
Answer.
They are the trio you
encountered in the cave.
Oh, right. Those guys.
Eating with her mask on... This girl I'm
destined to be with has some skills.
Guests, I fear we have little to offer,
but are you comfortable here?
Allow me to make introductions.
This is our master, the great Rimuru!
Master?
Got a problem with that?
Uh, no...
We knew you were no ordinary
slime, but we had no idea...
That threw them for a loop.
Maybe I should do something
to show them I'm harmless.
Nice to meet you! I'm Rimuru the slime!
I'm not a bad slime!
Shizu?
Huh? Did she actually get that joke?
We apologize.
We never expected to be saved by a monster,
but we do appreciate it.
Oh, and thanks for the meat!
It's delicious!
Th-Thanks for your help.
I didn't expect to find Goblins
building a village here.
She sure moves at her own pace...
So, what brings you all the way out here?
I'm Kaval. For what it's worth,
I'm the leader of this party.
This is...
I'm Eren!
Hello. I'm Gido. Nice to meet you.
And this is a temporary member who just
happened to be going the same way as us.
Shizu.
The one I'm destined to be
with is named Shizu, huh?
I guess she really is Japanese.
She's sitting seiza-style, even.
And?
We're here at the request of the
Guildmaster in the Kingdom of Blumund.
Kaval told me all of their plans, as if
he'd never learned to suspect anyone.
A Guildmaster in Blumund, one of the nations
bordering the Great Forest of Jura,
asked them to investigate the area.
I see.
Looks like Veldora's absence is having
a greater effect than I realized.
People are coming to check out not just
the cave, but all the surrounding area.
As you can see, we're in the
middle of building our village,
but, well... does the Guild
have some problem with that?
I don't think so. Right?
Yeah.
It's nothing the Guild has any say in.
What about the country, though?
I have no idea, myself.
I see. Well, I get it now.
You should stay here tonight
and get some good rest.
Thank you!
Treat them well.
Yes, sir!
Do you have a minute?
There's something I'd like to ask you.
Are you, um, from Japa—
Slime-san, that line you said
was from a game, wasn't it?
Huh?
"I'm not a bad slime."
I've never played it, but I heard about
it from someone else from my country.
Yeah!
I've been held by so many
women since I took this form!
One of the side perks, I guess!
Are you from Japan, too?
Yeah.
I see.
I'm glad I met you.
How did you come here?
Actually, I was stabbed to death.
Stabbed?
And the next thing I knew,
I had this magnificent form!
I see. So you were reincarnated.
That must've been hard.
Was it different for you?
I'm... a Summon.
A Summon...
That's right. Veldora talked about that.
It takes more than 30 mages to perform
a ritual that lasts several days
to bring one here from another world.
They're also expected to
serve as powerful weapons.
Magic is used to carve a
curse into the Summon's soul
to ensure that the Summon
can't defy the Summoner.
So... Shizu-san is a weapon?
And the curse...
I'm curious, but this probably
isn't the time to ask.
So when were you summoned here?
A long time ago.
My town was burning, engulfed in flames...
A war?
Bombs fell from the sky...
The air raids...
My mother and I fled together,
but then...
What happened to her?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, I know! I'll show you something fun!
Something fun?
Great Sage, I'd like to use
Thought Communication
to show Shizu-san some of my memories.
Understood.
Thought Communication
Here we go!
An elf?
No, no! It's not... It's not like that!
She was pretty.
Pretend you never saw that!
Look at this one!
Super Express Hikari
Wow...
It's like the skyscrapers of New York
that I saw on a picture postcard once.
After the war ended, peace came to Japan.
The towns and the economy all boomed.
I see... I'm so glad.
I wish I could have shown my mother this.
I want to make this world one where
everyone can live in peace, too.
That's wonderful. I hope it really happens.
It will! I'm sure of it!
Shizu-san?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
Hey, Rimuru!
Got a minute?
We'd like to talk to you about
where to build a new house.
Sure.
See you later.
See you.
Was I interrupting?
Shut up!
Now, don't be shy.
I'm not!
But you're blushing.
Mommy!
Another failure.
H-Help...
I thought she was useless, but she
may have an affinity for fire.
Ifrit, I offer her body to you.
Use it well.
Next time, "Conqueror of Flames."
Conqueror of Flames